[person] For me, WW is the Super Bowl.
我觉得 WW 就是超级碗
You can feel the energy.
你能感受到这种能量
[person] It's like really deep insights
就像深切了解
of what it feels like being a developer.
身为开发者的感受
[person] Really?
真的吗？
Wow.
哇
[person] Okay, we open on black.
好了 我们以黑色开场
The curtain slowly opens.
大幕缓缓拉开
Have a DeLorean on the stage.
一辆 DeLorean 停在舞台上
Tim Cook gets out of that DeLorean,
Tim Cook 从车内出来
showing the phone's flux capacitor.
展示手机的磁通电容器
[person] I would probably not start there.
我可能不会这么开场
I think it's kind of geeky.
这太极客了
[person] Cut!
卡！
[person] Are we going to go again?
是要重来一遍吗？
[person] So we open on black.
所以 我们以黑色开场
[person] Does it have to be black?
一定得是黑色吗？
It doesn't have to be black.
不必非得是黑色
[both] It could be yellow.
可以是黄色
[person] Now my mind goes into, like, a cartoon.
我脑海中就像在播放卡通片
[person] Imagine someone on their computer,
想象一下 有人在使用电脑
you know, they have an idea.
突然有了创意
And, like, they push, like, enter,
接着 按下 输入
or some red button and it goes out to the world.
或某一红色按钮 广为传播
And then all of a sudden, there's like millions of people
突然之间 全球有
around the globe that get to experience
数百万人可以体验到
the thing that you've made.
你的创作
Are you actually able to do all this?
你真能做到这一切？
[person] Um...
呃
[person] Maybe the title of the film
也许影片标题
should be "Our Journey Into Tomorrow."
应该叫“迈向明日之旅“
I see a little girl in an endless white room.
我看到一位小女孩站在无尽头的白色房间内
She meets Craig Federighi.
她遇到了 Craig Federighi
[Craig] Hi.
嗨
[person] But we don't see him.
但我们未见其人
We just hear his voice.
只闻其声
[Craig] Not cool.
不好吧
[person] Now she's older.
现在她长大了
And dressed for work.
还穿上了职业装
[person] There has to be action at this point
此时 必须有行动
or, like, some sort of drama.
或是 有某种戏剧性
She goes to work and discovers something catastrophic.
她刚到公司 就遇到突发情况
Someone says...
有人说道 我们遇到了 bug
[person] So she comes in
于是 她走进去
and pounds on the keyboard.
敲击键盘
And the bug is fixed.
修复了 bug
Yeah, it's like a musical.
是 就像音乐剧
[person] Musical?
音乐剧？
[person] Yeah, The Bug, But A Musical.
是 音乐剧 Bug
[person] Wait a minute.
等一下
Why not make arena rock of WW?
何不来场 WW 舞台摇滚？
There wouldn't be any pyro usually.
通常不会有烟火
But I think, why not?
但我觉得 为什么不呢？
Pyro is fun.
烟火多有趣
[person] Do you think it would work?
你认为这能行吗？
[person] Uh, you won't know if you don't try.
尝试过 才知道
[music continues]
为疯狂创想干杯
[Tim] Good morning.
早上好
And welcome to WWDC.
欢迎参加全球开发者大会 WWDC
It's so wonderful to see so many familiar faces
今天 很高兴看到这么多熟悉的面孔
with us today.
相聚于一堂
We're excited to share our latest technologies with you
我们很兴奋，能把我们的最新技术分享给你
and with the incredible community
和 Apple 全球开发者社区内的
of millions of Apple developers around the world.
数百万同行
Your creativity and groundbreaking apps
你的创造力和开创性的 app
continue to deliver new and meaningful ways
不断以全新和更有意思的方式
to enrich people's lives.
丰富大众生活
We applaud the extraordinary work
我们向你出色的成果致敬
you've been able to do
尤其在
throughout this challenging time.
这样挑战重重的时候
Last year's WWDC was our most inclusive
去年的 WWDC 是迄今包容性最强
and most watched developer conference ever,
收视率最高的开发者大会
with nearly 25 million viewers.
有近 2500 万观众
It was exciting to have so many people join us
很高兴有这么多人共襄盛会
and to see the impact it had on new Apple developers
并且亲眼目睹大会对 Apple 新的开发者带来影响
as we broadened our audience, welcoming more people
随着受众面更广
from more places around the world.
来自全球的人数和地域增加
We've continued to look for ways to help cultivate
我们一直在寻求有助于培养
the next generation of developers
新一代开发者的方法
with an emphasis on those underrepresented in technology.
特别是科技行业发声量不足的群体
We host entrepreneur camps for Black and female developers
我们非裔和女性开发者举办 Entrepreneur Camps
to foster the talents of future industry leaders.
培养未来的行业领袖
Our Developer Academies, including the newest in Detroit,
我们的 Developer Academies 包括最近在底特律新设的
prepare the coders of tomorrow
帮助未来的程序员们
with valuable tools and training.
获得重要的工具和培训
And Learn to Code offers an amazing curriculum
而 Learn to Code 开设精彩课程
for people to develop new skills and learn Swift.
帮助大家培养新技能和学习 Swift
We are committed to being a force for change
我们力争成为一支变革力量
as we seek to make the world a better place,
力求建设更美好的世界
full of opportunity for all of us.
人人都有各种机会
This year, we're bringing you another online experience
今年 我们将呈现另一种在线体验
featuring over 200 in-depth sessions,
举办 200 余场深度会议
one-to-one labs with Apple engineers,
与 Apple 工程师在实验室一对一交流
and so much more.
可谓精彩纷呈
We'll provide the tools you need
我们将提供多款工具
to continue creating the world's most innovative apps,
协助你不断打造世上最具创新力的 app
apps that inspire us in new ways every day.
每天以崭新方式激励我们前行
And just like last year's WWDC,
我们延续去年 WWDC 的做法
this entire conference will be made available for free.
今年的所有活动都免费开放
We've got a lot of exciting news and breakthrough innovations
今天 我们有好多喜讯和突破性创新
to share with you today.
要与你分享
So let's get started by turning it over to Craig
让我们马上开始 下面有请 Craig
to tell us what's new in iOS.
为我们介绍 iOS 的崭新功能
[Craig] Thanks, Tim.
谢谢 Tim
All right, let's dive right in.
我们开门见山
For many of us, our iPhone has become indispensable.
不知有多少人已离不开 iPhone
And at the heart of iPhone is iOS.
而 iPhone 的核心就是 iOS
iOS powers the experiences we've come to rely on.
我们全靠 iOS 营造非凡体验
This year, we were inspired to create
今年我们深受启发
even more meaningful ways iPhone could help you.
设计出更多有意义的方式发挥 iPhone 效用
Our new release is iOS 15.
我们最新的 iOS 15
It's packed with features that make the iOS experience
满载各项功能
adapt to and complement the way you use iPhone,
让 iOS 体验配合并完善你使用 iPhone 的方式
whether it's staying connected
无论是与
with those who matter to you most,
家人亲友保持联系
finding the space to focus without distraction,
找一处心无旁贷
using intelligence to discover the information you need,
运用智能技术 搜寻所需信息
or exploring the world around you.
探索身边世界
Let's start off with features that will let you
让我们先来看看以下功能
stay connected in brand-new ways.
以全新方式让你保持联系
In a year when figuring out how to get face-to-face
这一年 想办法面对面交流
has felt more essential than ever,
变得前所未有的重要
we've all found ourselves using video calling
我们凡事都会情不自禁
for just about everything,
使用视频通话
and when it comes to making calls that are easy,
如果谈到与家人亲友
spontaneous, and connect us with the people who matter most,
轻松自在通话 保持联系
FaceTime is a standout.
FaceTime 可是好手
With its incredibly intuitive design
凭借十分直观的设计
and end-to-end encryption since day one,
及始终秉持的端到端加密技术
FaceTime is how we catch up with friend around the world
无论是与世界各地的好友叙旧
and how we stay close to family members when we're apart.
还是与远方家人保持亲情 FaceTime 均能胜任
Enjoying these deeply personal moments over video
视频通话时 留下难忘时刻
can bring so much joy,
给我们带来许多快乐之余
but it also has its challenges.
也碰到不少难题
When talking in person, our brains process
当面交谈时 人类大脑会处理
hundreds of social, auditory and visual cues.
数百条社交、视觉和听觉线索
When talking on a video call,
视频通话时
many of those signals can get lost,
许多信号会丢失
leaving us feeling drained.
我们会疲惫不堪
So this year, we've set out to make FaceTime calls
今年 我们力图让 FaceTime 通话
feel more natural, comfortable, and lifelike.
更为自然、舒适和逼真
First is a feature that makes FaceTime calls
首先是让 FaceTime 通话
sound like you're sitting in the very same room.
效果如同双方共处一室的功能
We're bringing spatial audio to FaceTime,
我们为 FaceTime 带来空间音频技术
creating a sound field that helps conversations flow
营造的声场 让对话流畅
as easily as they do face-to-face.
如同当面交谈
Now your friends' voices are spread out
现在 你朋友们的声音会分布开
to sound like they're coming from the direction
传来的方向与在
in which they're positioned on the video call,
视频通话中的方位保持一致
making your calls more comfortable and more natural.
通话也更舒适和自然
Next, let's talk about two powerful new options
接下来 我们聊聊麦克风
for your microphone.
两个强大的新选项
The first is voice isolation.
第一项语音突显
When you're on a FaceTime call,
FaceTime 通话时
your mic is picking up a cacophony of sound,
麦克风会采集到好多声音
so in voice isolation,
开启语音突显
machine learning distinguishes those sounds,
机器学习会区分声音
blocks out the ambient noise, and prioritizes your voice
屏蔽环境噪音 让人声突显
so that it comes through crystal clear.
因而听起来更为清晰
Check it out.
我们来感受下
[person] I wish I could be there!
我希望我也在场
[person] Me too!
我也是
Let me fix this.
我来解决这个问题
Better, right?
好点了吗？
[person] Yeah.
是的
[person] Got what she wanted for her birthday.
得到了她想要的生日礼物
[Craig] Sometimes, though,
但有时
we want every bit of sound to come through,
我们希望声音点滴不遗漏
and that's when you switch to wide spectrum.
这时就要切换到宽频谱
In wide spectrum, your mic picks up
在宽频谱下 麦克风捕捉
an entire symphony's worth of sound:
整个环境中的声音
your voice and everything around you.
你的声音 还有周围一切声音
Next, let's turn to video.
接下来 我们来看视频
When you want to see every face in the room,
如果想看聊天室里的每张脸孔
you can now turn on grid view,
只需打开网格视图
giving you another way to view your group FaceTime calls.
换一种方式查看 FaceTime 群组通话
Here, you see people in the same size tiles,
每位成员的视频尺寸相同
and you'll be able to clearly identify who's speaking
你能清晰看到谁在发言
while seeing everyone else's reactions.
和每人各自的反应
And to make your FaceTime video capture
为了让 FaceTime 捕捉到
more beautiful than ever, we're introducing portrait mode,
更靓丽的视频画面 我们将推出人像模式
where we've taken inspiration
这一模式的设计灵感
from iPhone's stunning portrait photos.
源自 iPhone 人像照片的惊艳效果
In FaceTime, portrait mode blurs the background
使用 FaceTime 时 人像模式模糊背景
and naturally puts the focus on you.
你自然就成了画面焦点
Next, to help you schedule your FaceTime calls,
接下来 为了妥善安排 FaceTime 通话
we've created FaceTime links.
我们创造了 FaceTime 通话链接
Now you can generate a link for a FaceTime call
你可为 FaceTime 通话生成链接
and share it anywhere.
并分享至各处
It's a terrific way to plan ahead for a call.
是在通话之前安排妥当的好方法
You can send the FaceTime link in places like Messages, email,
你可以发送 FaceTime 通话链接到 信息 app、邮件、WhatsApp 中
WhatsApp, or jump into Calendar
或在日历 app 中
and make an event for your FaceTime call
为 FaceTime 通话创建日程
so everyone will know exactly where to meet and when.
这样大家都能确切知道在哪及何时见面
And it's not just Apple devices
并不只有 Apple 设备
that can use a FaceTime link to join your call.
才能通过 FaceTime 通话链接加入通话
Your friends with Android and Windows devices
即便朋友使用的是安卓或 Windows 设备
can use your FaceTime link to join the call
亦可通过 FaceTime 通话链接
right from their browser, and even on the web,
在浏览器中加入通话 即便是网页
FaceTime calls are still end-to-end encrypted,
FaceTime 通话依然采用端到端加密技术
so your privacy is never compromised.
隐私绝不会有丝毫泄露
Some of our favorite ways to connect
我们最喜爱的沟通方式
involve more than just talking,
远不止交谈一种
like getting together for a weekly movie night
还有每周佳片之夜
or listening to an album with a friend
或与好友共赏一张专辑
that brings back amazing memories.
回味往昔美妙时光
We love enjoying shared experiences,
我们喜爱共享体验
and so we built SharePlay.
因此打造了 SharePlay
SharePlay is a powerful new set of features
SharePlay 包含一系列强大全新功能
for shared experiences
带来共享体验
that you can enjoy when you're on a FaceTime call.
让你在 Facetime 通话时可以尽情享受
With SharePlay, you can bring music into your call
借助 SharePlay 你可在通话时播放音乐
for a shared listening experience unlike any other,
营造无与伦比的共享聆听体验
watch movies and TV shows
也可一边观看影片或电视节目
while having rich, real-time connection with your friends.
一边与好友实时沟通共享
And share your screen,
还可以共享屏幕
giving you limitless possibilities
带来无限可能
for bringing apps right into your FaceTime calls.
将各种 app 带入 FaceTime 通话中
Let me show you how this works,
我来演示一下
starting with listening together.
先从一起听歌开始
Say you're hanging out on a FaceTime,
如果你们在 FaceTime 上闲聊
talking about a new album that came out over the weekend.
谈论周末才发行的新专辑
With SharePlay,
有了 SharePlay
you could bring that album right into the conversation.
你可在交谈时播放这张专辑
When you're on a call, all you need to do
通话时 你只需
is press play in Apple Music,
在 Apple Music 中按下播放按钮
and you can choose to listen together.
即可选择一起听歌
And like magic, high quality music playback
如此神奇 高品质音乐
will start in sync for everyone on the call,
将为每位通话者同步播放
and you're still connected with FaceTime while listening.
你可以一边听歌 一边保持 FaceTime 通话
Everyone on the call can add songs to a shared queue,
每位通话者均可添加歌曲到共享的待播歌曲列表
and shared playback controls let anyone press play, pause,
还可共享播放控件 人人都能播放、暂停
or jump to the next track.
或切换曲目
Now let's check out what it's like to watch together.
现在 我们来看如何一起看片
When you're on a FaceTime call,
用 FaceTime 通话时
jump to streaming app and press play.
切换到流媒体 app 并按播放
and boom,
嘣
you and your friends are watching the same video
即可与好友一起观看同一个视频
totally in sync.
完全同步
SharePlay is unlike any other
SharePlay 呈现的
shared content experience out there
内容共享体验绝无仅有
because it moves fluidly throughout the whole system.
因为它在整个系统中流畅运动
Maybe you want to order takeout while you watch.
也许你想在观看的同时点外卖
Picture in Picture lets you see your friends
画中画功能 让你既可见到好友
and the video you're enjoying together,
亦可一起观看视频
and controls are always accessible
控制面板总在手边
with just a tap.
只需轻轻一点
And if the group wants to stay connected
如果大家想要保持沟通
with no interruptions to the video's sound,
又不想干搅到视频的声音
you can jump into Messages
你可以切换到信息 app
and keep the conversation going there.
继续在那里交谈
And when the moment calls for a bigger screen,
如需使用大屏
you can extend the video to your Apple TV
你可将视频扩展到 Apple TV
and watch it there while sharing the moment
观看视频的同时
with your friends over FaceTime on your iPhone.
使用 iPhone 在 FaceTime 上 与好友共享此时
Even when you're using SharePlay across multiple devices,
即便跨多台设备使用 SharePlay
everyone will remain in sync.
每位通话者依然保持同步
We wanted to make sure you have a ton
为了确保你能在 FaceTime 中
of incredible experiences to share in FaceTime,
共享许多美妙体验
so in addition to Apple Music and the TV app,
除了 Apple Music 和 Apple TV app
SharePlay is designed to work with
SharePlay 专为兼容
your other favorite apps and streaming services.
你喜爱的其他 app 和流媒体服务而设计
With an API built for easy adoption,
轻松借助 API
developers can bring their own apps right into FaceTime.
开发者可以将自己的 app 接入 FaceTime 通话
And today, we're so pleased to announce
今天 我们欣喜宣布
that we're already working with some incredible partners.
我们正与一些优秀的伙伴合作
Watch blockbuster movies with your friends on Disney+,
与好友在 Disney+ 上观看大片
and hit TV shows on Hulu.
在 Hulu 上观看热门电视节目
Catch originals from HBO Max.
观看 HBO Max 原创作品
And see your friends react live to a buzzer-beater
看到好友用 NBA app 看到压哨绝杀时
in the NBA app.
喜形于色
Or a speed run on Twitch.
在 Twitch 极速通关
Jump on TikTok to watch the funniest videos of the week,
在 TikTok 上观看本周最有趣的视频
learn a new skill with a friend on MasterClass,
在 MasterClass 上与好友一起学习新技能
and so much more.
精彩不断
Finally, check out screen sharing.
最后 来看屏幕共享
You can use it to browse Zillow listings
你可借助这一功能在 Zillow 上
live with your future roommates
和未来室友一起实时浏览房源
or show off a tricky move in your favorite game.
或秀出你在最爱游戏中的必杀技
Screen sharing is also a simple
屏幕共享也是一种简单
and super effective way to help someone out
又极为有效的方式 帮助别人
and answer questions right in the moment.
立刻解决问题
And it works across Apple devices.
还能跨 Apple 设备工作
So that's SharePlay, a whole new way in FaceTime
这就是 SharePlay 以全新方式在 FaceTime 通话中
to connect and share experiences with the people you love.
与家人好友保持联系和共享体验
Next, when it comes to staying connected throughout the day,
接下来 谈到如何全天保持联系时
our go-to is Messages,
信息 app 无疑是首选
and these days, so many of our conversations
当下 不知有多少交谈都以
are inspired through sharing articles, photos, and more.
共享文章、照片等作为谈资
So this year, we're introducing great new ways
今年 我们将以新颖方式
to enjoy all of this amazing shared content
尽情分享精彩内容
and the exchanges that follow.
并相互交流
Here's Mindy to show you how it all works.
下面有请 Mindy 为你演示
[Mindy] Thanks, Craig.
谢谢 Craig
I'm so excited to show you what's new in Messages.
十分荣幸为你展示信息 app 中的全新功能
Let's check out my family's conversation.
不妨来看我家的聊天界面
Everyone's sending me pictures
每位家人都在给我发
from our fun trip down to Joshua Tree.
加州约书亚树景区好玩的旅途照片
Look at this brand-new collage design.
请看全新的照片拼贴设计
And this cool stack with even more photos from Taylor.
还有很酷的堆叠方式容纳更多来自 Taylor 的照片
I can quickly swipe through them,
我可以快扫浏览
tap to view the full bunch,
轻点以查看全部
and add a quick Tapback.
并可快速添加“点回”
Now, let's see what's going on with my friends.
不妨来看与我朋友的聊天界面
They're always sending me all kinds of things,
她们总给我发各种各样的内容
like this fun playlist from Leah
比如 Leah 共享的有趣播放列表
and this mission critical article from Casey
Casey 共享的攻略文章
about what type of pizza is best.
介绍哪种披萨最好吃
The thing is, the time when I receive this great content
问题在于 收到这些很棒的内容后
is often different than when I'm ready to enjoy it.
通常没时间立马去欣赏
For example, I'm not going to read this right now,
比如 我暂时先不看这篇文章
but I'd love to the next time I catch up on the news.
等之后想补上的时候 再拿出来读
Let me show you something we designed just for that
我来为你演示专门为此设计的功能
called Shared with You.
与你共享
So now, if I head over to the News app,
前往新闻 app
there's a new Shared with You section
里边新增了与你共享板块
that conveniently surfaces that pizza article
便于我找出那篇介绍披萨的文章
and a few from my other friends.
以及其他朋友分享的文章
Now that I'm ready to learn more, I can take a look,
我想仔细了解时
and check this out.
就可以读一读 请看
Up top, it shows me who it's from.
顶部会显示共享人
And I can tap "from Casey" to pick up our conversation
我可以轻点“From Casey”接着聊天
and remind her that deep dish
提醒她芝加哥厚底披萨
is obviously the best kind of pizza,
显然最好吃
and then get right back to browsing.
然后继续浏览
So now, if I want to check out that playlist Leah sent earlier,
如果想听 Leah 早前发的歌单
I can head over to Apple Music.
我可前往 Apple Music
And it's right here.
在这儿
Let's take a listen.
我们来听一下
Love it.
真好听
Definitely adding this one to my library.
必须添加到曲库
Now, one I really love is photos.
我爱翻看照片
Remember those great pictures
还记得加州约书亚树景区之旅
from my family's trip to Joshua Tree?
我家人的那些美照吗？
Well, over in the Photos app, the new Shared with You section
照片 app 新增了 与你共享板块
makes it super easy to get back to them.
找到这些照片极为方便
They'll also appear in my featured photos and memories.
也会在精选照片和回忆中展示
And what's really cool is,
最棒的是
they're automatically brought over to my library too.
这些照片会自动归档到图库
So if I scroll back to that Joshua Tree trip,
如果我返回“Joshua Tree”
and drill in,
点进去
you can see all the great photos my cousin sent
就能看到我表亲发的所有美照
are right here with the ones I took,
还有我拍的美照
making my collection so much more complete with zero effort.
收集全照片 毫不费工夫
And Photos is smart enough to only bring over the ones
照片 app 很智能 只会归档
I actually care about, like the ones I was there for,
我最在意的照片 比如之前旅行的照片
so I don't have to worry
根本不必担心
about screenshots or memes cluttering up my library.
截图或表情包会弄乱照片图库
So that's sharing in iOS 15.
这就是 iOS 15 的共享功能
Back to you, Craig.
把镜头交还给你 Craig
[Craig] In addition to Photos, Apple Music, and News,
除了照片、Apple Music 和 News app
we've built Shared with You
我们把与你共享
into Safari, Apple Podcasts, and the Apple TV app.
集成入 Safari 浏览器、播客 app 和视频 app
And if something especially important comes through,
如果遇到了特别重要的内容
you can quickly pin it,
可快速置顶
and it will be elevated in Shared with You
即可在与你共享
and places like search.
和搜索等地方置顶
So that's Messages with Shared with You,
这就是信息 app 及与你共享
bringing connection to the places
为你串连起你喜爱的内容
you love to enjoy content.
便于尽享
Together with SharePlay
结合 SharePlay
and other powerful updates to FaceTime,
和 FaceTime 的其他实力更新
we're giving you even more meaningful ways to connect.
我们带给你更有意义的沟通方式
Of course, that means making the time for it,
当然 这就意味着要为此付出时间
so we have new tools
所以我们推出全新工具
to help you focus on what matters most.
帮助你专注在重要的事情上
Today, iPhone plays so many roles in our lives.
如今 iPhone 在生活中发挥着多重作用
It's where we get information, how people reach us,
获取信息 相互联系
and where we get things done.
完成任务
This is great, but it means our attention
这当然很好 但我们的注意力
is being pulled in so many different directions,
就被分散到了各个地方
and finding that balance between work and life can be tricky.
难以在工作和生活之间找到平衡
We want to free up space to focus
我们想腾出空间
and help you be in the moment,
有利于你专注当下
and that starts with notifications.
首先从通知开始
They have a fresh new look, contact photos for people,
拥有焕然一新的外观 联系人照片
and larger icons for apps,
app 图标变大
making them even easier to identify.
识别更轻松
Notifications are useful, though they can pile up
通知功能很有用 但一天下来
throughout the course of a day,
积聚了大量通知
breaking your focus in those moments
想要专心做事时
when you're trying to get in the zone.
却为此分了心
And the truth is, while some notifications
事实上 有些通知
require your immediate attention,
迫在眉睫
others could be dealt with later.
还有些通知则可以后续处理
To help you engage on your own time,
为帮助你安排自己的时间
we're introducing the notification summary,
我们将推出通知摘要
a helpful collection of your notifications
把通知集中起来
you can schedule to be delivered at any time you choose,
你可以自行选择何时推送
like in the morning and evening.
比如在早晨或者晚间
We use on-device intelligence
我们运用设备端智能技术
based on how you interact with your apps
根据使用 app 的习惯
to arrange the summary
组织摘要内容
so it's easy to quickly catch up.
便于你迅速把握要点
Notifications in the summary are ordered by priority,
通知摘要按优先级排序
with the most relevant ones rising to the top.
越靠上 相关性越高
Notifications from people will not end up in the summary,
联系人的通知不会出现在摘要里
so you won't miss important messages as they come in.
这样你就不会错过重要消息
If now really isn't a good time,
如果现在实在不方便
you can use Do Not Disturb to silence all notifications.
你可以打开勿扰模式将所有通知静音
And it turns out, it's even easier to step away and focus
其实 退到一边做自己的事很容易
if people know we're busy,
如果大家知道我们确实在忙
so we created an easy way
所以我们创造了一个简单的方法
to signal to others when you're doing that.
告诉对方你正忙
Now when you're using Do Not Disturb,
现在使用勿扰模式时
your status is automatically displayed in Messages.
信息 app 会自动显示你的状态
When you reach out to someone
如果你想联系
who's indicated they don't want to be disturbed,
不希望受打扰的人士
you'll be reminded in that moment.
你当即就会被提醒
And for truly urgent messages, there's a way to get through.
若真有急事 依然可以发信息给对方
While an important part of finding focus
寻求集中注意力
is about reducing distraction from others,
不单是希望减少他人打扰
it's also about drawing boundaries for yourself.
更是为自己设定界限
There may be periods in your day
一天当中 总有时候
when you want to be totally focused on work,
想一心扑在工作上
or maybe you just want to be fully present
或许想与家人私享
with your family at dinner.
美妙晚餐时光
In these moments, you can use Do Not Disturb
遇到上述情况 你可开启勿扰模式
or strike more of a balance with Focus.
或用专注模式去做平衡
Focus is a new way to match your device
专注模式以全新方式让你的设备
to your current mind-set.
匹配你当前的心境
With Focus, all you have to do
有了专注模式 你只需
is choose what you want to focus on.
选择想要关注的内容
You can carve out time in your day
你可在一天内划分出
for work or your personal life.
工作或私人生活时间
When setting up a Focus, we use on-device intelligence
设置专注模式时 我们运用设备端智能技术
about your past activity to suggest the apps and people
根据你的活动规律 建议为哪些 app 和联系人
to allow notifications from.
开启通知
So if you're at work, you could choose
如果你在工作 可以选择
to only be notified by coworkers
仅允许同事 或邮件 app、日历 app
or apps like Mail, Calendar, or Slack.
Slack app 等发送通知
You can even dedicate a page on your home screen
你还可以在主屏幕上设置专用页面
to match your focus
契合你的专注点
and organize your apps and widgets
并有序组织 app 和小组件
in a way that reduces temptations
来减少分心
by making only your work apps visible.
如仅让工作 app 可见
For personal life, we'll suggest being notified
私人时间里 我们建议只收取
only by friends and family or apps like Calm.
家人朋友或 Calm 这类 app 发送的通知
And for a home screen to match,
匹配主屏幕时
you can have your favorite entertainment apps like YouTube
可以放上 YouTube 等心爱的娱乐 app
or widgets for keeping up with your friends and family.
或与家人好友保持联系的小组件
We'll even intelligently suggest using a Focus
我们甚至还会智能建议开启专注模式
based on your context,
依据当前情况
using different signals like location or time of day.
分析各种因素 如地点或时间
Of course, you can create a custom Focus too.
当然 你亦可创建自定义专注模式
And when you use a Focus on one device,
当你在一台设备上使用专注模式
it automatically sets on all your other devices.
其他所有设备都会自动设定
We think together, these tools
我们认为 综合运用
are a really powerful way to help you find balance.
上述工具 能有效帮助你找到平衡
Not only does iOS give you space to focus,
iOS 不单给你空间专心致志
it also uses intelligence to elevate your experience,
还运用智能技术 提升使用体验
helping you discover more in your photos,
帮助你在照片中发现更多
quickly find what you're looking for,
快速找到想找的内容
and even relive special moments.
甚至重温特别时刻
Let's get started with a feature we call Live Text.
先介绍一项全新功能实况文本
Today our photos are full of rich and useful information,
如今的照片 信息丰富且有价值
from photos of places we visit
无论是拜访的地点
to handwritten notes of family recipes.
还是家庭食谱上的手写笔记
And now Live Text unlocks this information
现在 实况文本能解读照片中的信息
in a way that's really natural.
用一种极为自然的方式
It starts with the camera.
先看相机 app
Let me show you.
我来演示
Let's say I just finished a meeting with the team,
假设我刚结束团队会议
and I want to capture my notes from the whiteboard.
想拍下我在白板上的笔记
I can now just point the camera at the whiteboard
只需将摄像头对准白板
and an indicator appears here in the lower right.
右下角就会有指示
When I tap it, the text just jumps right out.
轻点一下 文字出现
I can use my normal text selection gestures.
我可以使用常规的文本选择手势
Just drag and copy.
只需拖动和复制
Now I can switch over to Mail and paste those in
我可以切换到邮件 app 把文字粘贴进去
and then send this off to Tim.
发送给 Tim
How cool is that?
棒不棒？
And this is great for photos already in your photo library.
这也适用于图库中的照片
Here's a photo of a friend.
这张我朋友的照片
You may notice that here at the top there's some text.
你可能注意到 顶部这里有一些文字
Now, I can just select it, like this,
我可以直接选取 就像这样
and I have the option to use Look Up
我也可以选查询
to find out more about this restaurant
详细了解这家餐厅
and even look up its location.
还能查找位置
Oh, and here's a picture from a friend.
这里有一张我朋友拍的照片
Now, you may notice here in the background,
你可能会注意到背景中
is a phone number.
有一个电话号码
I can just zoom in, and with Live Text,
只需放大 使用实况文本
it's recognized with a link.
识别并生成链接
I can just tap it and give this place a call,
轻点一下 即可拨打这家餐厅的电话
just like that.
就像这样
[person] Hi, Wanderlust Creamery.
你好 Wanderlust Creamery 餐厅
[Craig] Oh, uh, whoops. Sorry.
哎呀 抱歉
Uh, just applying a deep neural network here
刚才我在用深度神经网络
to a photo of your shop.
用了一张你们店的照片
No actual need for ice cream at this time.
现在不是真的要冰激凌
Uh, gotta drop. Bye.
挂了 再见
Live Text works with photos across the entire system,
实况文本可识别整个系统中的照片
including screenshots, Quick Look,
包括截图 快速查看
and even photos on the web.
甚至网页上的照片
And it understands seven languages,
实况文本可识别七种文字
including simplified and traditional Chinese,
包括简体中文和繁体中文
and works across iPhone, iPad, and Mac.
iPhone、iPad、Mac 都适用
And it's not just text.
不单是文本
You can also look up information
还可识别物体和场景
on recognized objects and scenes.
并查找相关信息
Just tap, and you can look up information,
只需轻点 即可查找信息
like the breed of a dog or type of a flower.
例如狗或花的品种
And this works for art, books, nature,
艺术品、书籍、大自然
pets, and landmarks.
宠物和地标均可识别
We're also making it easier to search for your photos
我们也让搜索照片变得更方便
by adding photos to Spotlight.
在聚焦搜索加入了照片
Spotlight is the universal place
聚焦搜索是通用的
to start all of your searches.
一切搜索的起点
Now, with photos search in Spotlight,
现在 在聚焦搜索里加入了照片
you can quickly find your photos right from the home screen.
你就可以从主屏幕直接迅速查找
Spotlight leverages intelligence from the Photos app,
聚焦搜索运用照片 app 的智能技术
so you can search by people, scenes, elements in your photos,
你可按人物、场景、照片中的元素
or location, like San Francisco,
进行查找 或按地点如旧金山
And leveraging Live Text,
利用实况文本
Spotlight can even find text in your photos,
聚焦搜索还可查找照片中的文字
which is great when you're looking for a photo
特别方便 尤其当你要找
of a recipe, a receipt, or even a handwritten note.
收据、食谱甚至手写便条
We've also added all-new rich results for contacts.
我们还为通讯录新增了丰富的查找结果
You'll have quick access to call, text,
你可以快速访问电话、文本
FaceTime, or email them
FaceTime 通话或发邮件
and Spotlight intelligently includes
聚焦搜索可智能收录
everything related to them:
一切相关信息
their location, if shared through Find My,
他们的位置 如果已通过查找 app 共享
recent conversations, shared photos,
近期聊天记录、共享照片
calendar appointments, notes, and files.
日历预约、备忘录、文件
And we've added all-new rich results
我们也为演员
for actors, musicians, TV shows, and movies as well.
音乐家、电视节目和电影新增了丰富的查找结果
That's Spotlight.
这就是聚焦搜索
Next, let's talk about how Photos
接下来 我们聊下照片 app
uses its deep understanding of what's in your library
如何利用对于图库照片的深度理解
to enable powerful, emotional features like Memories.
实现回忆等极具情感色彩的功能
Memories intelligently curates your favorite moments,
回忆会智能精选精彩时刻
stitching photos and videos together
将照片和视频连缀成
into heartfelt movies.
感人的影片
To take a closer look at what's new, here's Chelsea.
下面有请 Chelsea 详细介绍全新功能
[Chelsea] Thanks, Craig.
谢谢 Craig
This year we've got the biggest update ever,
今年 我们迎来迄今最大更新
including bringing Apple Music into your Memories
包括将 Apple Music
for the first time.
首次融入回忆
Let me show you.
我来为你演示
Here in the Photos app, I can tap on the For You tab,
我先启动照片 app 再轻点为你推荐标签
and my Memories are right at the top.
顶部即呈现回忆
Check out this beautiful new animated title card.
看看这新的动画标题卡片好漂亮
Let's watch this one of my climbing adventures.
不妨来欣赏我的登山冒险集锦
You'll hear a relevant, personalized song
你将听到一首又合拍又适合我的音乐
from Apple Music that brings the memory to life.
来自 Apple Music 让回忆生动起来
These new memories are built on the fly.
这些新回忆是即兴生成的
They're interactive and alive
动态交互 画面生动
and are paced to the beat of the music.
并和着音乐节拍
I can tap and hold to pause,
我可以轻点不放 画面暂停
and the music continues to play.
音乐则继续播放
When I let go, the pacing adjusts to get back on beat.
我松开手指 画面会重新跟上节拍
And to see a photo again,
如果还想看上一张照片
all it takes is a swipe.
只需轻扫一下
To customize my memory, I'll use a new feature
如果要自定义回忆 我会使用全新功能
called Memory Mixes.
回忆混音
I can tap to bring up the controls
先轻点屏幕 调出控制面板
then tap this button to jump in.
再轻点这个按钮进入
Swiping on this carousel lets me try out different mixes
轻扫这个轮播图 尝试不同组合
with intelligently chosen songs, pacing,
组合会智能选择相互匹配的
and a look to match.
歌曲、节奏、效果
Notice how the feel of the memory changed
注意这段回忆的感觉发生了变化
with a calmer song, slower transitions,
当切换到更平和的音乐、更缓慢的过渡
and a black and white look.
以及黑白的效果
[singing] It's hard to believe
[♪ ♪]
[Chelsea] This faster song has a more energetic feel.
这首快歌听起来活力满满
And these looks aren't just filters.
呈现这些画面效果 不单靠滤镜
We analyze each photo
我们分析每张照片
and apply consistent color and contrast,
运用一致的色彩和对比度
just like a colorist at a film studio.
就像电影工作室的调色师
To check out more intelligent song suggestions,
如果想查看更多智能选歌建议
I'll tap on the music button.
只需轻点音乐按钮
You'll notice these top suggestions
你会发现这些置顶建议
are a great fit for my climbing Memory.
都十分契合我的登山回忆
With tens of millions of songs in the Apple Music Library,
从 Apple Music 资源库数千万首歌曲中
experts have curated sets of songs
专家们精选成集
that are combined with my music tastes
结合我的音乐品味
and the knowledge of what's in my photos
和照片分析
to create personalized recommendations just for me.
为我创建个性化推荐
I can search for a specific song
我也可搜索特定歌曲
by tapping on the magnifying glass,
只需轻点放大镜图标
but I'm gonna go with something from my listening history.
但我想从听歌历史记录里选歌
This song from Imagine Dragons will be perfect.
Imagine Dragons 乐队的这首歌很合适
[singing] 'Cause I'm on top of the world, hey
[♪ ♪]
And I can keep watching related memories,
我可以继续观看相关回忆
personalized with my favorite songs from Apple Music.
伴随 Apple Music 中的心仪歌曲
And now back to Craig.
把镜头交还给 Craig
[Craig] With Live Text, Look up, Spotlight, and Memories,
凭借实况文本、查询、聚焦搜索和回忆
iOS 15 elevates the iPhone experience
iOS 15 提升 iPhone 使用体验
with on-device intelligence.
充分运用设备端智能技术
Next, let's talk about how iOS helps you better understand
接下来 我们聊下 iOS 如何帮助你更好了解
and explore the world around you,
和探索身边世界
with some great updates to Wallet, Weather, and Maps.
以及钱包 app、天气 app、地图 app 的一些出色更新
To tell us about what's new in Wallet, here's Jennifer.
下面有请 Jennifer 介绍钱包 app 的全新功能
[Jennifer] With the Apple Wallet app,
Apple 推出钱包 app
we set out to replace your physical Wallet.
旨在取代实体钱包
Starting with Apple Pay,
首先是 Apple Pay
we added payment cards to make payments safer and more secure.
我们增加了支付卡 实现更安全 更有保障的支付
Next, we brought transit cards with Express Mode
之后 我们把快捷交通卡
to your iPhone.
带到了 iPhone 上
You just breeze through the turnstiles in San Francisco,
你可以快捷搭乘公共交通
New York, Beijing, Tokyo, and more.
在旧金山、纽约、北京、东京等地
You can never leave home without your keys,
出门一定要带钥匙
so we're continuing to add keys to Wallet
我们将陆续添加钥匙到钱包 app
and making them even better.
营造更为完善的使用体验
We started with car keys,
我们先看车钥匙
which we're improving with Ultra-Wideband support
我们采用超宽带技术
for an unlock and drive experience.
增进对开锁和驾驶体验的支持
No need to take your iPhone out of your bag or pocket.
无需从手袋或口袋里拿出 iPhone
BMW and others will ship cars with UWBs
宝马等汽车品牌将推出支持超宽带的车型
starting later this year.
预计于今年晚些时候陆续问世
With iOS 15, we're bringing keys for your everyday places
有了 iOS 15 钱包 app 将新增面向日常地点的钥匙
to Wallet, starting with where you live.
先从生活场景开始
We're creating the fastest, most secure way
我们创建最快速 最安全的方式
to unlock your house, apartment, or flat,
来为别墅、公寓
and where you work.
和你的工作场所解锁
Just add your corporate badge
只需添加工牌
and tap to enter your building or office.
轻点即可进入大楼或办公室
And where you travel, with hotel keys.
外出旅行 就会携带酒店客房钥匙
You'll automatically receive your key
你会自动收到钥匙
when your room is ready,
当你的客房准备就绪
even before you arrive at the hotel.
即便还未抵达酒店
Starting this fall, Hyatt hotels will start rolling this out
从今秋起 凯悦酒店集团将陆续
to over 1,000 properties worldwide,
在全球千余家酒店推出这项服务
creating a faster and safer experience for their guests.
为宾客营造更快捷 更安全的入住体验
Anywhere you go, just tap to unlock.
无论去到哪里 只需轻点即可开锁
have signed on to support keys for all the places you go.
与我们签订了钥匙支持协议 畅通无阻行天下
However, to be fully free of your physical wallet,
但要想完全摆脱实体钱包
there's one more thing we need to bring to iPhone,
还有样东西要引入 iPhone
and that's your ID.
这就是身份证件
So we're bringing identity cards to Apple Wallet.
身份证件不久将可添加到 Apple 钱包
This fall, you'll just scan your driver's license
今秋 在美国参与计划的几个州
or state ID in participating US states.
只需扫描自己的驾照或州身份证即可
It's that easy.
就这么简单
Your ID information is now in Wallet,
钱包 app 内的身份证件信息
encrypted and safely stored in the Secure Element,
加密并安全存储于 Secure Element
the same hardware technology
采用与 Apple Pay 相同的
that makes Apple Pay private and secure.
硬件技术 保证隐私和安全
And the TSA is working to enable airport security checkpoints
TSA 正在努力让机场安检站
as the first place you can use your digital ID.
率先接纳数字身份证件
When you present your ID,
当你出示身份证件时
you'll know what specific information is requested
你知道哪些具体信息是需要的
and securely presented.
并且以安全的方式出示
With just a tap, you're off to your flight.
只需轻点一下 即可登上航班
So that's Wallet on your iPhone and Apple Watch.
这就是 iPhone 和 Apple Watch 上的 钱包 app
Back to you, Craig.
把镜头交还给你 Craig
[Craig] Next up, weather.
接下来介绍天气 app
The Weather app is incredibly popular,
天气 app 十分受欢迎
and it's getting a huge update.
将迎来大幅更新
First, we're introducing a beautiful new design
首先 全新设计很精美
with data and layouts that change based on conditions
数据和布局会根据
such as wind and rain, unhealthy air quality,
风雨、不健康空气质量、晴天
or sunny skies.
等天气情况变化
We've also added new weather graphics
我们还添加了全新天气图形
to help users better understand conditions
有助于用户更好了解
like wind, UV index, and barometric pressure.
风、紫外线指数、气压等天气情况
And we've completely redesigned
我们完全重新设计了
the gorgeous animated backgrounds.
精美的动画背景
There are now thousands of variations
有数千种变化
that more accurately represent
更准确呈现
the sun position, clouds, and precipitation.
太阳方位、云朵和降水
And Weather app in iOS 15
iOS 15 中的天气 app
includes full-screen, high-resolution weather maps.
还加入了全屏高清天气地图
These maps show temperature,
天气地图显示
animated precipitation, and air quality
温度、降水动画和空气质量
that provide a whole new way to see the weather around you.
以全新方式呈现身边的天气
Next, we have some really big updates
接下来 另一款日常所需的 app
for another app our users depend on every day.
也将迎来大幅更新
Apple Maps.
地图 app
Apple Maps is the best way to navigate your world.
地图 app 堪称出行导航的最佳选择
It's easy to use and beautifully designed,
使用便捷 设计精美
while providing the confidence that your privacy is protected.
同时能确保你的隐私信息受到保护
Here's Meg to tell you more.
下面有请 Meg 为你详细介绍
[Meg] Two years ago, we started rolling out our new map,
两年前 我们开始推出全新地图
offering richer details and more accurate navigation
提供了更丰富的细节和更精致的导航
to help you get around.
来帮助你
Built from the ground up, we've launched our new map
我们从零开始打造 全新地图
so far in the U.S., UK, Ireland, and Canada,
迄今已在美国、英国、爱尔兰和加拿大推出
and we're excited to announce
我们欣喜宣布
we're bringing the new map today to Spain and Portugal,
西班牙和葡萄牙将于今天启用全新地图
and later this year,
今年晚些时候
we'll add Italy and Australia.
意大利和澳大利亚也会加入
Our goal has always been to build the world's best map.
一直以来 我们始终致力于打造最出色的地图 app
So we looked at everything we've done so far,
回顾过往一切努力
and we asked ourselves, "How can we push things even further?"
我们问自己 怎样能做得更好
We started by building a gorgeous, interactive globe
首先我们构建了一个精美的可互动地球
that invites users to tap and explore.
鼓励用户轻点来探索
This is a whole new way of looking at the world.
这是一种看世界的新方式
But it's in cities
而在城市里
where we're taking Apple Maps to an entirely new level.
我们将地图 app 的使用体验进一步提升
Our current map is great, and our users have told us
现行的地图 app 已经很出色 很多用户表示
it's a lot more useful for navigation and exploration,
可以很方便地进行导航和探索
but in iOS 15, Maps will offer incredible new details
而 iOS 15 的地图 app 将呈现
for commercial districts, marinas, buildings,
商业区、码头、建筑等的
and so much more.
全新丰富细节
We've added things like elevation,
我们增加了不少元素 例如海拔
new road colors and labels,
全新道路颜色和标签
as well as hundreds of custom-designed landmarks
以及专门设计的数百个地标
for places like Coit Tower and the Golden Gate Bridge.
像是柯伊特塔和金门大桥
And we built a beautiful new nighttime mode
我们还全新构建了夜间模式
with a moonlit glow.
带有月光特效 十分优美
We think all of these improvements
我们觉得 对于地图 app 用户
are going to make exploring a city
所有这些改进
so much fun for Maps users.
将令城市探寻之旅乐趣横生
And when a user is ready to go somewhere,
用户准备出行时
Maps in iOS 15 will make getting there way better.
iOS 15 的地图 app 将带来了更好的导航体验
Let's start with driving.
让我们从开车开始
We've added a great deal of new road details to the map
我们在地图上增加了大量全新道路细节
so we can help drivers as they move throughout a city,
帮助驾驶员在城市中穿行时
to better see and understand important things
能更好注意和了解
like turn lanes, medians, bus and taxi lanes, and more.
转弯车道、中央隔离带、巴士车道 出租车道等重要路况
This outstanding attention to detail,
我们对细节的关注
including the addition of crosswalks and bike lanes,
包括增加了人行横道和自行车道
will help drivers more safely navigate complex intersections.
帮助驾驶员更安全通过复杂路口
And when driving on highways, Maps now renders
在高速公路上行驶时
overlapping, complex interchanges
地图 app 现可渲染
in three-dimensional space,
复杂的立体交叉道
making it much easier to see upcoming traffic conditions
帮你更容易了解前方路况
or to know which lane you need to be in.
或需要行驶于哪个车道
And of course, we'll be bringing this driving experience
当然 今年晚些时候
to CarPlay later this year.
我们也会为 CarPlay 车载系统带来这种驾驶体验
But it's not just driving.
除了开车导航
We've also made big improvements for transit riders
搭乘公交的导航体验也有了大幅改进
by helping them easily find nearby stations.
帮助大家轻松找到附近的车站
Users can pin their favorite lines to the top
用户可以把选择的线路置顶
and even keep track on their Apple Watch
还可以在 Apple Watch 上持续追踪
so there's no need to take your phone out of your pocket.
而无需从口袋里拿出手机
Maps also automatically follows your transit route,
地图 app 还会自动追随行车的路线
notifying you it's time to disembark
快要到达终点站时
as you approach your final destination.
会通知你下车
And if you've ever exited a station,
出站之后
unsure of which direction you need to go,
如果不知道去往哪个方向
Maps will help get you back on track.
地图 app 将为你指路
Simply hold up your iPhone, scan the buildings in the area,
只需拿出 iPhone 扫描前方建筑
and Maps will generate a highly accurate position,
地图 app 将生成极为准确的定位
delivering detailed directions in augmented reality
用增强现实技术 显示详尽的步行路线
to help you complete your journey.
帮助你步行抵达目的地
We're launching this beautiful new three-dimensional experience
这种新颖又优美的三维导航体验
in these cities by the end of 2021,
2021 年底前 将在屏幕上的这些城市将推出
with many more to come next year.
明年还会有更多城市加入
And that's the all-new Apple Maps.
这就是全新的地图 app
Back to you, Craig.
把镜头交还给你 Craig
[Craig] So that's just some of what's new in Apple Maps.
这只是地图 app 的部分全新功能
An incredible new way to explore the natural beauty of the world,
全新方式探索地球的自然之美
and an amazing new three-dimensional
令人惊艳的全新三维城市
city experience with improved navigation.
带来优化的导航体验
iOS 15 is a great release that helps you stay connected,
iOS 15 带来的诸多重大更新 包括帮助你保持联系
find focus, discover more with on-device-intelligence,
让自己更专注 运用设备端智能技术发现更多精彩
and explore the world.
探索世界
And there's more, including Voice Search in Safari,
不仅这些 还有 Safari 浏览器的 语音搜索功能
powerful support for cross-app drag and drop,
支持不同 app 间的内容拖放
and new outfit options for Memoji.
为拟我表情带来全新装束选项
So that's iOS 15,
这就是 iOS 15
with powerful new features that enhance how you use iPhone.
带来了各项强大新功能 优化 iPhone 的使用体验
And of course, one of the most popular
当然 我们最受欢迎的
accessories for iPhone is AirPods.
一款 iPhone 配件要数 AirPods
To tell you more about what's new, here's Gagan.
下面有请 Gagan 为你详细介绍新功能
[singer] ♪ Party for you ♪
[♪ ♪]
[Gagan] AirPods have helped us enjoy music like never before,
AirPods 让我们以全新方式来欣赏音乐
and they've helped us stay connected
更以丰富的方式让我们保持连结
in so many different ways, whether to friends and family,
无论是与家人朋友
to our devices, or to our favorite entertainment.
与我们各类设备 还是与我们喜爱的娱乐内容
With iOS 15, we have some great new features coming to AirPods,
iOS 15 同样为 AirPods 带来一些出色的新功能
starting with Conversation Boost,
首先介绍 Conversation Boost
which is designed to help people with mild hearing challenges
帮助轻微听障人士
stay more connected in conversations.
顺畅交谈
Through computational audio and beamforming microphones,
借助于计算音频和波束成形麦克风
Conversation Boost focuses your AirPods Pro
Conversation Boost 将 AirPods Pro
on the person talking in front of you,
聚焦于面前的交谈对象
making it easier to hear and follow along
当面交谈时
in a face-to-face conversation.
帮助你让容易听清对话
And to help you hear the conversation even better,
为了帮助你更好听清谈话
you can also reduce the amount of ambient noise.
你还可以降低环境噪音
Next, when you can't reach for your iPhone,
接下来 无法拿到 iPhone 时
Announce Messages with Siri helps you stay connected.
Siri 的信息播报功能可以帮助你保持联系
iOS 15 takes this further with Announce Notifications.
iOS 15 在此基础上有进一步发挥 带来了通知播报功能
Now Siri can automatically read
Siri 现可自动为你朗读
your important, time-sensitive notifications to you,
具有时效性的重要通知
like when your dinner has been delivered.
比如你的晚饭外卖已经送到了
And when you set a location for your Reminder,
如果你在提醒事项 app 里设置了地点
like the grocery store,
比如你到了超市
Siri will read your shopping list to you
Siri 可以为你朗读你的购物清单
right when you need it.
在你需要的时候
You can easily choose which Apps to enable
你可以自己选择哪些 app 启用这个功能
and select Do Not Disturb
如果不想受打扰
when you don't want to be interrupted.
也可以选择勿扰模式
And if you're using the new Focus feature,
而当你选择全新的专注模式时
your notification preferences are already taken into account.
你的通知偏好设置已考虑在内
Next, we have significantly improved
接下来 我们显著改进了
how AirPods work in Find My.
AirPods 在查找 app 中的工作方式
With iOS 15, you can locate your AirPods Pro and AirPods Max
在 iOS 15 中 你可以定位自己的 AirPods Pro 和 AirPods Max
using the Find My network.
并利用查找网络
Your AirPods simply send out a secure Bluetooth beacon
AirPods 发出的安全的蓝牙信标
that can be detected by other Apple devices.
能让其他的 Apple 设备测检到
They can relay your AirPods' location to the network
并将 AirPods 的位置传到查找网络中
and then back to your Find My app.
再回传给你的查找 app
And if they're nearby, just choose Play Sound.
若在附近 只要点选播放声音
Listen for the chirp, whether they're in their case or out.
无论是否在充电盒内 只需听啁啾声
And the new proximity view in the Find My app
查找 app 新增了距离视图
lets you know when you're getting close.
你靠近时 会显示提示
To make it even less likely to lose your AirPods,
为了尽量避免丢失 AirPods
you can now receive a Separation Alert
你会收到遗落提醒
to notify you if you leave your AirPods behind.
通知你 AirPods 忘拿了
Finally, last year, we introduced spatial audio
最后 我们去年为 AirPods Pro
with dynamic head tracking for AirPods Pro
带来具有动态头部跟踪的空间音频
and then elevated the experience even further
并将这样的体验进一步提升
with the high fidelity audio of AirPods Max.
带来了高保真音效的 AirPods Max
Enabled by computational audio,
依托于计算音频技术
the three-dimensional theater-like sound
影院般的立体声体验
really makes movies come to life.
为你带来身临其境的观影体验
This fall, we're excited to extend spatial audio to tvOS.
今年秋天空间音频技术也会来到 tvOS
So now you can enjoy the full surround experience,
你可享受全方位环绕声
tuned for the big screen in your living room,
专为你的客厅大屏幕萦绕
without disturbing the rest of the house.
不会打扰家里其他人
And with dynamic head tracking,
有了动态头部跟踪
it properly responds as you move about the room.
你在室内走动时 空间音效也会随时调整
We're also bringing spatial audio with dynamic head tracking
搭载全新 M1 芯片的 macOS
to macOS on our new M1 powered Macs
也将支持带有动态头部跟踪的空间音频
so you can enjoy spatial on all of your devices.
这样 你在各个设备端均可享受空间音频
In addition, we recently announced spatial audio
此外 我们近期宣布
for Apple Music with the incredible
Apple Music 对空间音频的支持
multi-dimensional sound experience of Dolby Atmos.
发挥杜比全景声震撼的多维音效
And we're excited that it's available starting today
我们很高兴从今天起 这一功能将由
with albums from some of your favorite artists,
许多你喜欢的音乐人的专辑呈现
like Ariana Grande, The Weeknd, J Balvin, and Kacey Musgraves.
包括 Ariana Grande、The Weeknd J Balvin、Kacey Musgraves 等
With the benefits of Conversation Boost,
有了 Conversation Boost 的便利
the convenience of Find My,
查找功能的便捷
and the enhanced experience with spatial audio,
空间音频带来的优化体验
there are some great new features
AirPods 系列
coming to the AirPods family.
着实新增了不少出色功能
Now back to you, Craig.
把时间交还给你 Craig
[singer] ♪ Just like magic, oh, yeah ♪
[♪ ♪]
[Craig] It's time to talk about iPadOS.
是时候来聊聊 iPadOS 了
iPad is an incredibly versatile device,
iPad 是一个拥有令人惊叹的多用性设备
with its unique blend of mobility,
同时兼备独一无二的移动性
innovative technologies, and touch-first user experience,
诸多突破创新的技术和触控优先的使用体验
and this experience is powered by iPadOS.
而这种体验正是由 iPadOS 驱动的
With iPadOS, we build distinct capabilities
基于 iPadOS 我们打造了各种独特功能
that make it possible for iPad
让你的 iPad 在你需要时
to become whatever you need it to be,
随时变身成为你趁手的工具
like when you're browsing your photos
当你用来浏览自己的照片时
and iPad becomes an album of your most precious memories,
你手中的 iPad 就是收藏
held right in your hands;
最珍贵记忆的相册
or when you pick up Apple Pencil
当你拿起 Apple Pencil
and it becomes your notepad, a markup tool,
iPad 就成了记事本 标记工具
or a canvas for new artwork;
或者你下一个艺术创作的画布
or when you attach a keyboard and trackpad,
当你连上键盘和触控版
and it becomes a powerful new way
iPad 就带来了功能强大的新方式
to work on your most important documents.
帮你处理手头的重要文档
This unique set of capabilities
这一系列独特的强大功能意味着
mean you get things done right in the moment
你能随时随地即时完成手上的事
and can seamlessly move
从捕捉灵感
from capturing and working on your ideas
形成创想 到及时共享
to sharing them.
一气呵成
With iPadOS 15,
iPad OS 15 旨在
we're taking this versatility further,
将这样的多用性进一步延展深化
making iPad even more capable and more intuitive,
让 iPad 变得更强大 且更直观易用
and we started right on the home screen with widgets.
让我们直接从主屏幕的小组件开始
They offer beautiful, glance-able information
它们让各类信息精美呈现
at just the right moments,
并在需要的时间让你一目了然
and this year, we have a big update.
今年 我们将为之带来大幅更新
Now you can freely place widgets
现在你可以自由将各种小组件
among the apps on your home screen.
排放在主屏幕的各类 app 间
This is a huge deal!
很了不起
Let me show you how it works.
我来演示具体操作
Okay.
好的
Here I am on the home screen.
现在我就在主屏幕上
You can see that I already have a few widgets
你可以看到 这里已经有一些小组件
placed along the top.
排列在顶端
Let's start by adding a widget.
让我们从添加一个小组件开始
I'll bring up the widget gallery.
让我调出小组件栏
Here you'll notice some new widgets
这里你注意到一些全新的小组件
like the beautiful new Find My widget
例如精美新设计的查找 app 的小组件
and the Contacts widget
还有通讯录 app 的小组件
which helps you reach family and friends
当你需要联系家人或朋友时
with just a tap.
只需轻点一下
Let's find a good spot for this, towards the top here.
让我们为它找个好位子 移到顶部这里
Now, I'll go back to the gallery and grab the Parcel widget
现在我回到小组件栏 Parcel app 的小组件
for tracking my incoming packages
用来追踪我的快递
right on the home screen.
直接在主屏幕上
Now, of course a bigger canvas means more room for widgets,
当然 更大的屏幕 也意味着给小组件的空间也越大
so we're adding a new, larger format for widgets
所以 我们新增了一个更大的小组件尺寸
designed just for iPad's larger display.
专为 iPad 更大的显示屏而设计
Here's the new Apple TV widget.
这是全新视频 app 小组件
I can easily dive into my favorite shows with a tap,
轻点一下 就能直接进入我在追的剧
and here's my gaming page.
这一屏都是我的游戏
The new Game Center widget
全新 Game Center 小组件
lets me jump into my games faster
让我更快进入我的游戏
and discover what to play with friends.
探索能与朋友玩什么游戏
And check out the new large-size Photos widget.
来看看全新的大尺寸照片 app 小组件
It really puts my favorite photos front and center,
把心仪照片放在醒目处
and with this larger Files widget,
而更大尺寸的文件 app 小组件
I can keep tabs on all of my work projects.
可以呈现我各类工作文件的标签
Now, with pages full of these great widgets,
前面这些实用的小组件占据了好几屏
some of my less frequently used apps
一些不常用的 app
have gotten pushed to later pages.
就被排到后面了
We wanted to make it easier to get to all of your apps,
为了更轻松访问所有 app
so we brought App Library to iPad.
我们将 App 资源库也带到了 iPad 上
You can see all my apps are here,
我的所有 app 都在这里
automatically categorized for me.
并都自动分好类别了
And what's really cool is we built access to App Library
更棒的是 我们将 App 资源库的入口
right into the Dock,
直接设计在程序坞上
no matter where you are,
这样无论你在哪一屏
you can always get to your apps.
都可以快速找到你需要的 app
And now that you have App Library,
有了 App 资源库
you can hide pages that you no longer need...
你可以隐藏那些你不需要的 App 页面
just like this.
就像这样
And even reorder them right from here.
或者像这样重新排序
That's widgets and App Library.
这就是小组件和 App 资源库
We think this is going to change how you get information
我们相信 这将改变你在 iPad 上
and access all your apps on iPad.
读取信息及访问各类 app 的方式
We also have a major update
我们还带来一个重大更新
for another key part of the iPadOS experience:
来提升 iPadOS 体验的另一关键环节
multitasking.
多任务处理
This year, we've made it easier to discover,
今年 我们让这个体验变得更容易发现
easier to use, and even more powerful.
更易用也更强大
To give you a closer look, here's Shubham.
下面有请 Shubham 为你详细介绍
[Shubham] Thanks, Craig.
谢谢 Craig
In iPadOS 15, there's a new control
在 iPadOS 15 中
that appears at the top of your apps.
在各个 app 的上方都会有一个新的控件
Tapping on it reveals the multitasking menu.
只需轻点 就可以调出多任务处理的菜单
From here, I can take an app, full-screen,
在这里 我可以让一个 app 全屏显示
or work with two apps at the same time
也可以让两个 app 同时运行
by creating a Split View or Slide Over.
可以创建分屏浏览或者侧拉来实现
I'll tap on the Split View icon,
轻点分屏浏览图标
and the app slides to the edge of the screen,
当前 app 就会自动滑到屏幕边缘
giving me quick access to my home screen,
让我能快速回到主屏幕
where I can easily select from any of my apps.
从中选择我需要的 app
I've been working on a podcast, so I'll choose Ferrite.
例如我在制作播客 所以打开 Ferrite app
And now I can work with Ferrite and Notes
现在我就可以同时打开 Ferrite app 和备忘录 app
at the same time in Split View.
通过分屏浏览来进行工作
It's also really easy to switch apps in Split View.
在分屏浏览中切换 app 很方便
If I want to replace Ferrite, I just swipe down,
若要替换 Ferrite app 只需向下轻扫
and Notes moves aside,
备忘录 app 移到一侧
letting me pick another app from the home screen.
就可以从主屏幕上挑选另一款 app
Let's select Mail.
我们选择邮件 app
This works exactly the same way
选择新 app 的操作方式
to choose a new app from either side of the screen.
在屏幕两侧是完全相同的
And we brought the same ease of multitasking
我们将多任务处理的便捷用法也带到了
to apps with multiple windows.
支持多窗口的各类 app
In Mail, I can touch and hold on this message
在邮件 app 中 轻点并按住这封邮件
to open it centered on my screen.
即可在屏幕中央打开
This allows me to read the entire email
无需离开当前视图
without leaving my current view.
即可阅读整封邮件
And I have the same multitasking controls here, too,
这里同样有多任务处理控制面板
so I can easily move this into Split View or Slide Over.
可将这个窗口轻松移入分屏浏览或侧拉
But I want to save this email and come back to it later.
但我想保存这封邮件 稍后再看
So I can just swipe down to minimize it
只需向下轻扫
into a new area we're calling the Shelf.
将窗口最小化至新的 App 架区域
The Shelf gives me easy access to all open windows of an app.
App 架让我可以轻松访问 一个 app 所有打开的窗口
Let's go to Safari, and you'll see that
我们前往 Safari 浏览器
the Shelf appears automatically when I switch apps.
当我切换 app 时，当前 App 的 App 架会自动显示
I often have a lot of Safari windows open,
我通常会打开多个 Safari 浏览器窗口
many in Split View paired with other apps,
许多窗口是和其他 app 分屏浏览的
and now I can just tap to quickly switch between them.
只需轻点 即可快速切换
I can also add or remove windows right here from the Shelf.
我还可以在 App 架中随时增减窗口
We've also made the App Switcher even more powerful.
同时我们让 App 切换器变得更为强大
I can now create a Split view
例如我要创建分屏浏览
just by dragging one app over another.
只需把一个 app 拖到另一个 app 上就行
So that's multitasking in iPadOS 15.
这就是 iPadOS 15 中的多任务处理
Now back to you, Craig.
把镜头交还给你 Craig
[Craig] Thanks, Shubham.
谢谢 Shubham
These new multitasking features
上述全新多任务处理功能
will help our users be more productive
将帮助用户更高效
and do even more on their iPad,
在 iPad 上完成更多事务
and what's really cool
此外更棒的是
is we now have a new set of keyboard shortcuts
我们推出一套全新键盘快捷键
that let you do all of this without lifting a finger.
不用抬手 轻松完成各类操作
iPadOS 15 also gives you more powerful ways
在 iPadOS 15 中 你还能以更多巧妙方式
to capture and organize your information with Notes.
使用备忘录 app 来记录并整理各类信息
This year we're adding powerful new features
今年 我们新增了诸多强大的新功能
for collaboration and organization.
便于协作及组织管理
First, we're adding mentions.
首先 我们增加了 @提及功能
Just mention someone in a shared note
只需在共享备忘录中 @提及某人
and they'll get a notification linking them back.
此人就会收到通知 以便查看提及之处
There's also an all-new Activity View
还有全新 Activity View
that quickly shows you what's changed
让你快速查看共享备忘录中的改动
in a shared note while you were away.
即便是你离开的时候
And to give users new ways to organize their notes,
还有新的方式让用户来整理自己的备忘录
we're adding tags.
也就是新增的标签功能
You can add a tag anywhere in your note
你可以在备忘录的任意地方添加标签
then use the new Tag Browser to quickly find your notes.
然后用全新的标签浏览器迅速找到对应的备忘录
But sometimes you just want to quickly jot down a note
有时候你只想赶紧记下重要的事
to remember something important for later,
以备不时之需
and that's why we're taking Notes system-wide
所以我们推出了系统级的新功能
with a feature we call Quick Note.
快速备忘录
Quick Note is a fast and easy way to get to a note,
这个功能让你可以快捷打开一个备忘录
no matter what you're doing.
无论你正在做什么
Here's Will to show you how it works.
下面有请 Will 为你演示
[Will] Thanks, Craig.
谢谢 Craig
Starting a Quick Note is easy.
要调出快速备忘录 非常简单
When I swipe, the note appears
像我这样轻扫
out of the corner of the screen.
备忘录就从屏幕的角落出现了
Now that I've started a note,
我打开了一个备忘录
I can type or write with Apple Pencil.
可输入 也可用 Apple Pencil 书写
It's perfect for jotting down something like a phone number.
十分适合快速记下电话号码之类
And when I'm done, I just swipe it away.
记好之后 将备忘录轻扫掉
Let's open Safari.
我们打开 Safari 浏览器
What's super cool about Quick Note
快速备忘录超赞的是
is that it's aware of the app I'm using.
可识别我在使用的 app
I'll start a new Quick Note on top of Safari...
我在 Safari 浏览器上新加了一个快速备忘录
...and now I can easily add a link from the website
我可以非常便捷地将一个网页链接
into my Quick Note.
添加到快速备忘录里
I can tap this link anytime to return to this exact site.
我可以随时轻点这个链接 回到这个网页
Let's go to a website I added a link to earlier.
让我们来访问我之前添加过链接的网站
A small thumbnail pops up in the corner
这时角落里出现的小缩略图
that allows me to quickly get back to my Quick Note
便于我随时回到快速备忘录
containing any useful information I found.
这里记下了各种我需要的信息
You'll notice there's text highlighted on the page.
你会注意到页面上的一些高亮文本
And I added this text to my Quick Note.
我已经把这段文本添加到快速备忘录中
And tapping on a link from a highlight
而当我轻点高亮文本的链接
takes me right to the content on the page.
就可以直接回到页面上相应的内容
I can add a link from almost any app I'm using,
我可以添加几乎任何 app 中的链接
including third-party apps.
包括各类第三方 app
Here's a link from Yelp, and if I tap,
这里有个 Yelp 链接 我轻点一下
it takes me right to the restaurant listing.
直接就能打开餐厅的页面
I can swipe across my Quick Note
我可以在快速备忘录中轻扫
to see my most recent ones.
切换我最近的备忘录
And anytime I want to see all my Quick Notes,
如果要查看我所有的快速备忘录
I can find them right where you'd expect, in Notes.
访问备忘录 app 即可
Now back to Craig.
把镜头交还给 Craig
[Craig] Thanks, Will.
谢谢 Will
So that's Quick Note,
这就是快速备忘录
a new way to capture information anywhere.
全新方式来记下各类信息
Quick Notes can be created on iPadOS and macOS,
快速备忘录可以 在 iPadOS 和 macOS 中创建
and you can access and edit them later on iOS.
稍后在 iOS 上访问和编辑
Now let's talk about Translate.
现在 我们聊下翻译 app
In just one year, Translate has already helped users
仅仅一年 翻译 app 帮助用户们
make billions of translations on iOS.
在 iOS 中进行了数以十亿计的翻译
So we're excited to bring Translate to iPad,
很高兴 现在翻译 app 也来到了 iPad
with experiences that leverage iPad's unique capabilities,
并依托 iPad 的独特功能带来出色的体验
like practicing handwriting in another language
例如练习手写外国文字
with Apple Pencil
可以用 Apple Pencil
or translating right next to your document
或以分屏浏览
with Split View.
对照翻译文稿
And Translate was designed for conversations.
翻译 app 的设计初衷是为了帮助沟通对话
So we're making conversations feel easier
所以为了让对话更容易更自然
and even more natural with Auto Translate.
我们推出了自动翻译功能
Auto Translate detects when you're speaking,
自动翻译功能会识别你是否在讲话
and in which language,
讲的是哪种语言
so no one needs to tap a button to respond.
所以大家不需要在每次说话前必须点个按键
Just speak and let Translate do the rest.
只需直接开口 其余交给翻译 app 完成
We're also excited to announce system-wide translation.
我们很高兴将翻译功能延展到全系统
So you can translate text anywhere.
让你可以翻译各处文本
Just select the text and tap Translate.
只需选取文本并轻点“翻译”
With Live Text, you can even translate text in a photo.
有了实况文本 你还能翻译图片中的文字
System-wide translation is available
全系统翻译功能在
on iPadOS, iOS, and macOS,
iPadOS、iOS 和 macOS 中都可以使用
and of course, you can download languages
当然 你可以下载语言包
to use all of these features on-device.
在设备端使用所有功能
Whether you're working on a document
无论是处理文稿
or meeting with someone,
还是亲自见面
Translate makes iPad even more powerful.
翻译 app 让 iPad 的功能更强大了
Now let's talk about Swift Playgrounds
现在 我们聊下 Swift Playgrounds
and how it's bringing a whole new dimension of productivity
以及它将怎样把全新维度的生产力
to iPad.
带到 iPad 上
Swift Playgrounds is a great way to learn to code
Swift Playgrounds 是学习编程的绝佳方式
through a series of Apple-designed lesson plans
只需跟着 Apple 设计的一系列课程计划
that are interactive and fun.
让编程学习充满了互动性和趣味性
This year we're taking it even further
今年 我们在此基础上更进一步
by adding the ability to build apps on iPad.
让你直接在 iPad 上编写 app
You build these apps with Swift UI,
你可使用 Swift UI 编写 app
which makes development easy.
Swift UI 让 app 开发变得非常简单
The code you write is immediately reflected
你写的代码可以即刻
in a live preview of your app.
在 app 实时预览呈现
This new project type even works with Xcode on Mac.
这一全新的项目类型也和 Mac 版 Xcode 兼容
Swift Playgrounds now supports improved code completion,
Swift Playgrounds 现支持优化的代码补全
so you can just start typing
只需直接输入代码
and quickly add the suggestion to your code.
并为代码快速添加建议
You also have access to the whole library
你还能访问整个 UI 组件
of UI components
资源库
and the documentation to go with it.
及配套文档
And if you're new to app development,
如果你是 app 开发新手
there's a guide to creating your first app.
还有创建首个 app 指导可参考
While you're developing your app,
开发 app 时
you can run it full-screen to try it out,
你可以全屏试运行
and when you're ready,
当你准备就绪时
you can even submit it to the App Store.
可以直接提交 App Store
This is amazing!
太妙了
You can now build apps for iPhone and iPad on iPad.
你可以直接在 iPad 上 开发各类 iPhone 和 iPad 的 app
We think this will take iPad to new places.
我们相信这将翻开 iPad 的新篇章
That's iPadOS 15,
这就是 iPadOS 15
taking the versatility of iPad even further
将 iPad 的多用性推向新的境界
with new widget layouts for your home screen,
为主屏幕带来全新小组件布局
App library, and a redesigned multitasking experience,
App 资源库 重新设计的多任务处理体验
new note-taking and translation features,
全新笔记和翻译功能
and the ability to build apps with Swift Playgrounds.
使用 Swift Playgrounds 来开发 app 的能力
Combined with the great new features we talked about in iOS,
加上我们之前聊到的 iOS 的各项新功能 也会出现在 iPadOS
it's time to completely rethink what you can do with your iPad.
是时候重新审视怎样充分发挥你手中的 iPad 了
Next, let's get into Privacy.
接下来 我们了解下隐私功能
At Apple, we believe privacy is a fundamental human right.
在 Apple 我们认为隐私是基本人权
We don't think you should have to make a trade-off
我们认为
between great features and privacy.
你不应在出众功能和隐私之间取舍
We believe you deserve both.
我们认为你能两者兼得
Since the beginning,
从一开始
we've worked to help you keep your personal data
我们就努力帮助你将个人数据
under your control.
在自己控制之下
And over the years, we've integrated
多年来 我们将卓有成效的
powerful privacy controls
隐私控制
into our operating systems, most recently adding
集成入操作系统 最近新增了
Privacy Nutrition Labels and App Tracking Transparency.
隐私标签和 App 跟踪透明度
Today, privacy is more important than ever,
今天 隐私比以往都更重要
because when you use the internet
这是因为当你使用互联网和
and third-party apps, you can be tracked
第三方 app 时
by a complex ecosystem of data brokers
数据公司和广告技术公司构成的
and ad tech firms, often without your permission.
复杂生态系统会跟踪你 通常未经你允许
We don't think this is right.
我们不认可这种做法
We believe in protecting your privacy
我们认为要保护你的隐私
and giving you transparency and control
给予你对自己信息的
over your information.
透明度和控制权
And to tell you about the new ways
下面有请 Katie 和 Erik
we're giving you even more control,
介绍给予你更多
here are Katie and Erik.
控制权的全新方式
[Katie] Thanks, Craig.
谢谢 Craig
Let's start with Mail.
我们从邮件 app 开始
If you're like me, you get a lot of marketing emails like this.
你可能会像我一样 收到许多这样的营销邮件
What you may not realize is that many of these emails
你可能没有意识到 其中许多邮件
use invisible pixels
利用隐形像素
to collect information about your Mail activity,
收集你的邮件活动信息
like when you open a message and even your IP address.
比如你何时打开邮件 甚至你的 IP 地址
We think you should be able to choose
我们觉得 你应能够选择
whether to allow this or not.
是否允许收集信息
So now in the Mail app,
我们将为邮件 app
we're introducing Mail Privacy Protection.
带来邮件隐私保护功能
Here's what it does.
其作用如下
It hides your IP address so senders can't link it
它隐藏你的 IP 地址 这样发件人就无法关联
to your other online activity or determine your location.
你的其他线上活动 亦无法确定你的位置
And it prevents senders
它可以阻止发件人
from seeing if and when you've opened their email.
了解你是否及何时打开了邮件
So now you can catch up on email with greater peace of mind.
这样 你查收邮件的时候可以更安心
[Erik] Safari leads the industry
Safari 浏览器凭借
in protecting you against cross-site tracking
智能防追踪保护功能
with Intelligent Tracking Prevention,
在防范跨站点跟踪方面业内领先
and this year, we're making it even stronger
今年 我们更进一步
by also hiding your IP address from trackers
阻止跟踪者获取你的 IP 地址
so they can't use it
因此他们无法用来
to link your activity across different sites
关联你在其他站点的活动
or learn your location.
或解析你的位置
You can see which trackers are prevented from profiling you
你可在 Safari 隐私报告中看到
in the Safari Privacy Report.
哪些追踪器被阻止对你进行分析
We wanted to bring this same transparency
我们希望为你使用的 app
to apps you use too.
带来同样的透明度
[Katie] So we're introducing the App Privacy Report.
因此 我们将推出 App 隐私报告
This new section in Settings
这些新增加的设置功能
gives you an overview of how apps treat your privacy.
可以让你概览 app 如何处理你的隐私
You can see how often apps use the permission you've granted
你可查看过去 7 天里
to access your location, photos, camera, microphone,
app 利用你的授权 访问位置、照片、相机
contacts, and more, during the last 7 days.
麦克风、通讯录及其他数据的频率
And to find out who your data may be shared with,
要了解你的数据可能与谁共享
you can see all the third party domains the app is contacting.
你可查看这款 app 正在联系的所有第三方域名
So these are our new privacy system controls.
这些是我们全新的隐私保护控制系统
Now let's talk about Siri.
现在 我们聊下 Siri
Siri's available across all your Apple devices,
Siri 在所有 Apple 设备上提供
allowing you to quickly get things done
只需发出语音
with just your voice.
就能迅速完成任务
And Siri is being used more than ever
Siri 使用量与日俱增
on over 600 million devices each month.
每月有 6 亿余台设备在使用
We recently added more diverse Siri voice options,
我们近期丰富了 Siri 语音选项
and they sound incredible.
声音效果很棒
[Siri] Hi, I'm Siri. If you need anything, just ask.
你好，我是 Siri 你需要什么，尽管开口。
[Katie] Now, Siri has a ton of great new features this year,
今年 Siri 会有许多出色的新功能
but today we want to focus on a major update to privacy.
但今天 我们想重点介绍隐私方面的重大更新
[Erik] Siri's designed to process
Siri 力求尽可能
as much data on device as possible,
在设备上处理数据
keeping your information private,
保护信息私密
and with the power of the Neural Engine,
加上神经网络引擎的威力
we're able to do this more than ever.
数据安全更胜以往
Today we're introducing on-device speech recognition.
我们将引入设备端语音识别技术
This means that, by default,
这意味着，在默认情况下
your audio is all processed right on your iPhone or iPad.
你的音频完全在 iPhone 或 iPad 上处理
This addresses the biggest privacy concern we hear
这样就消除了对于语音助手的
for voice assistants, which is unwanted audio recording.
最大隐私疑虑 杜绝不必要的录音
And this has some great benefits beyond privacy.
而且这个功能在保护隐私之余 还有一些非常好的益处
First, you can now make many requests
首先 即使没有互联网连接
without an internet connection:
也可以发出许多请求
launch apps, change settings, control music, and more.
启动 app、更改设置、控制音乐等
Second, on-device processing speeds things up.
其次 设备端处理 加快进程
Check this out.
请看
I'll do a few requests back to back.
我会连续发出请求
Open Photos.
打开照片 app
Open Calendar.
打开日历 app
Turn on Airplane Mode.
开启飞行模式
Set a timer for 20 minutes.
定时器设置为 20 分钟
Switch to dark mode.
切换到深色模式
Wake me up at 7:00 a.m.
早上 7 点叫醒我
It's amazing how fast Siri is with on-device processing.
Siri 在设备端飞快的处理速度 令人叹服
So those are some of the powerful
这些就是邮件 app
new privacy protections in Mail, Safari, and your apps,
Safari 浏览器和你的 app 中 一些出众的全新隐私保护功能
along with on-device speech recognition for Siri.
及面向 Siri 的设备端语音识别技术
Back to you, Craig.
把镜头交还给你 Craig
[Craig] Next, another part of our ecosystem
接下来 在我们的生态系统中
that puts your privacy first is iCloud.
iCloud 同样把你的隐私放在首位
Here to tell you about some great new updates is Mike.
下面有请 Mike 为你介绍一些出色的更新
[Mike] Many of us rely on iCloud
许多用户都依靠 iCloud
to safely store a lot of personal information,
安全存储许多个人信息
and it's important to always have access.
而且必须始终能访问
So let's start off with two improvements
我们先介绍将为 Apple ID
we're making to your Apple ID.
带来的两项改进
First, we're adding a new way to get back into your account
首先 我们增加了一种全新方法 如果你忘记了
if you forget your password or get locked out.
密码或账户锁定 可以重新登录账户
You'll now have the option to add people you trust,
你可以选择添加家人好友等
like your family and friends, to a Recovery Contact list.
值得信赖的联系人到 恢复联系人列表
They won't get any access to your account,
他们访问不了你的账户
but if you ever forget your password,
但要是你忘了密码
you can call them to get the code you need
可以打电话给他们 获取重新登录账户
to get right back in.
所需的认证码
It's fast, easy, and secure.
快速、简单、安全
Second, we're launching a new Digital Legacy program.
其次 我们将推出全新电子遗产计划
We don't often think about it,
我们不会经常思考这个问题
but it's important that we can easily pass down
但我们身故之后
information to family members or friends when we pass away.
一定得便于把信息传给家人好友
You'll now be able to add people to your account
你可以把个人作为
as Legacy Contacts.
遗产联系人添加到账户
So when you're gone, they can simply request access,
你离世以后 他们立马就能请求访问
and your information can be passed along
而且传输你的信息
quickly and easily.
迅速方便
iCloud has always kept your important information--
iCloud 始终保证照片、文稿
like photos, documents, and notes--
备忘录等重要个人信息
safe, up to date, and accessible across all of your devices,
安全、最新且所有设备均可访问
and today, we're making some big updates.
今天 我们将带来一些重大更新
We're upgrading our paid subscription
我们将付费订阅
to something that we call iCloud+.
升级为 iCloud+
iCloud+ combines everything you love about iCloud
iCloud+ 综合 iCloud 的所有优点
with some great new features,
和一些出色的全新功能
starting with something to help protect your privacy online.
首先来看有助于保护线上隐私的功能
On any given day, we all use a variety of networks
每一天 我们都会使用各种网络
to browse the web:
来浏览网页
from the internet in our own homes.
无论是自家的互联网
to public Wi-Fi on the go.
还是旅途中的公共 Wi-Fi
And behind the scenes, network providers and websites
在后台 网络服务商和网站
can combine your identity and browsing history
会综合你的身份信息
into a detailed profile about you.
和浏览历史记录 生成你的详细档案
So now, in addition to everything that Safari does
除了 Safari 浏览器尽力
to protect you online, we are introducing a new service
保护你的线上隐私 我们还推出全新服务
called Private Relay.
Private Relay
It lets you browse with Safari
你可以更安全 更私密
in an even more secure and private way.
使用 Safari 浏览器浏览内容
And the way it works is really cool.
其工作方式十分巧妙
It ensures that the traffic leaving your device is encrypted
它确保对流出设备的流量加密
so that no one can intercept and read it.
没人能拦截和阅读
Then all of your requests
所有请求都要通过
are sent through two separate internet relays.
两个独立的互联网中继发送
It's designed so that no one, including Apple,
包括 Apple 在内 没有人
can see both who you are
知道你是谁
and what sites you're visiting,
也不知道你在访问什么站点
and it does all this without compromising performance.
实现所有功能的同时 性能丝毫不受影响
Next, let's talk about another iCloud+ feature: Hide My Email.
接下来 我们聊下 Cloud+ 的另一项功能 隐藏邮件地址
We've all had moments when we've thought twice
需要共享个人电子邮件地址时
about sharing our personal email address,
我们都会慎之又慎
like when we're filling out a form on the web.
比如 填写网络表单时
With Hide My Email, you can share a unique, random address
有了隐藏邮件地址 你可共享随机生成的唯一地址
that forwards messages to your personal inbox.
便于将邮件转发到个人收件箱
It's built right into Mail, Safari, and iCloud Settings.
这项功能内置于邮件 app Safari 浏览器和 iCloud 设置
So it's easy to set up as many addresses as you need
以便按需轻松创建数量不限的地址
and delete them at any time, keeping you in control.
随时可以删除 一切尽在掌控
iCloud+ also includes built-in support
iCloud+ 还包括内置支持
for HomeKit Secure Video.
HomeKit 安全视频
More and more of us are using security cameras
越来越多用户使用安防摄像头
to keep an eye on our homes.
监控家中情况
With iCloud+, you can connect more cameras than ever,
有了 iCloud+ 你可以连接比以往更多的摄像头
and none of the video counts against your iCloud storage.
所有安防视频均不计入 iCloud 存储容量
It's just a part of your subscription.
这是你订阅的一部分
Of course, you'll still get
当然 你依然能获得
everything else you love about iCloud,
其他所有你钟爱的 iCloud 功能
including Photos, Backup, and iCloud Drive.
包括照片、备份、iCloud 云盘
And the best part is we're not changing our prices at all.
最喜人的是价格未变
You'll get all of iCloud plus our new Private Relay service,
你可使用 iCloud 所有功能 外加全新的 Private Relay 服务
Hide My Email and expanded HomeKit secure video support
隐藏邮件地址 和 扩充后的 HomeKit 安全视频支持
for the same low price as we offer today.
同现在的价格一样低
We're really excited to be giving users
我们十分高兴
an even more private and connected experience
iCloud+ 能给用户带来更加私密
with iCloud+.
和互联的体验
Now over to Sumbul for the latest developments in Health.
下面有请 Sumbul 介绍健康 app 的最新进展
[Sumbul] Your health and the well-being of your family
你和家人的健康
is always important to you,
始终对你很重要
and never more so than this past year.
过去一年更是至关重要
Apple's commitment to health is stronger than ever.
Apple 比以往更注重健康事业
We're collaborating with medical experts
我们携手医学专家
to accelerate health innovation,
加速健康创新
and we're empowering individuals to improve their health
我们竭力赋能 改善个人健康
as well as make it easier for them to participate
更便于他们参加
in large-scale research studies.
大规模研究
With our APIs,
通过我们的各类 API
developers are using our devices and Health app
开发者将使用我们的设备和健康 app
to come up with ingenious ways to push things forward.
以独创性的方法推动医学发展
Here's an example.
这里举个示例
[Francoise] I’m Francoise Marvel.
我叫 Francoise Marvel
I’m a cardiology fellow at Johns Hopkins.
约翰·霍普金斯医院的心脏病学研究员
[Seth] Seth Martin.
我叫 Seth Martin
I’m also a cardiologist at Johns Hopkins.
也是约翰·霍普金斯医院的心脏科医生
[Francoise] Seth and I spend our days
我和 Seth 每天都在
alongside our patients at the bedside.
治疗卧病在床的患者
You know, six white coats, hovering over a bed.
六位医生共同治疗一位患者
And we’re trying to actually share
我们尽力去分享
what the patient’s condition is.
患者的病情
How they need to improve their life.
讨论他们需要如何改善自己的身体状况
We use medical jargon. We speak quickly.
我们使用医学术语 讲得飞快
We confuse patients.
患者为此深感困惑
And they’re left on their own.
感觉孤立无助
There has to be a better way than just treating a patient,
一定有一种办法胜过单纯治疗患者
handing them a bunch of papers, and expecting
递给患者一堆文件
We thought, well, what if we completely reengineer
我们思索 不如彻底重新设计
the process for a heart attack patient, by using ResearchKit,
心脏病患者的治疗流程
that help us to know patients are doing well.
帮助我们了解患者病情发展
[Seth] When Francoise was in the technology accelerator program
Francoise 参加了约翰·霍普金斯技术加速器计划
at Hopkins, the work there led to this phone call with Apple
她在那里的工作促成了这个与 Apple 团队的电话
Francoise said to Divya at Apple, “What can we do
Francoise 对 Apple 的 Divya 说道
[Divya] You guys gotta come out to Cupertino.
你们得来库比蒂诺
[Francoise] And we had a Silicon Valley AirBnB.
我们在硅谷找了间 Airbnb 民宿
And we started side-by-side coding with our iOS developers,
开始与 iOS 开发人员
and then every couple hours--
每隔几小时
[Divya] We would talk about their vision
大家就会讨论创想和可以利用的工具
[Francoise] We’d go to a white board, and we’d lay out--
我们会去看白板并列出
[Divya] Here are the things you guys should go tackle.
这些事情你们应该去解决
[Francoise] And we’d go back to our AirBnB, pour more coffee,
然后回到 Airbnb 民宿
And then we would go into Cupertino.
然后 我们再去库比蒂诺
[Divya] They’d come back into Cupertino, piled in a minivan.
他们开着一辆小货车 回到库比蒂诺
[Francoise] And spend like almost the full day there,
几乎花上一整天时间
getting more feedback, working with their teams.
获得更多反馈 与他们的团队合作
[Divya] They would leave our offices,
他们离开我们的办公室
and work through the night
整夜工作 建立和实施
With our tools and their vision,
我们的工具结合他们的创想
we ultimately made magic together.
最终共同创造了奇迹
[Francoise] We left Cupertino invigorated, and guess what?
离开库比蒂诺时 我们精神抖擞
Our clinical trial was able to save
我们的临床试验能够拯救
an incredible amount of people from having complications
大量患者 避免出现并发症
and coming back to the hospital.
和再次入院
And it reduced hospital readmissions by 52%.
再住院率降低了 52%
And likely saved a lot of lives.
可能挽救了许多生命
[Divya] I remember we were just sitting outside--
我记得我们当时坐在室外
beautiful Cupertino weather.
库比蒂诺景色如画 气候宜人
And it was just one of those moments where it dawned on us
这只不过是其中一个瞬间 让我们感悟到
that Corrie app was going to have an impact
Corrie app 一定会呵护
on so many people’s hearts around the world.
世界上很多人的心脏
[Francoise] This is the start of something incredible.
这一不可思议的旅程从此开始
It’s the spark, and now it’s like fire
它从一点火花已经变成了烈焰
[Sumbul] This is just one of the many inspiring stories out there
这只是众多鼓舞人心的故事中的一个
and is a testament to the innovative work happening
证明医学界在努力
in the medical community.
锐意创新
A critical part of taking care of yourself
监测自己的健康变化
is monitoring changes in your health,
是照顾好自己的一项重要组成部分
which can be subtle and easy to miss over time.
可这种意识会随着时间逐渐淡薄和遗忘
So this year, we're offering three new features
今年 我们将推出三项新功能
to help you to identify, measure,
帮助你识别 测量
and understand those changes, and here's Adeeti
和了解这些变化 下面有请 Adeeti
to tell you about the first of these features.
为你介绍其中第一项功能
[Adeeti] Let's start with mobility.
我们先来看“活动能力”
The way that you move and walk
你的移动和行走方式
can indicate balance issues and gait impairment.
可表明平衡问题和步态障碍
This is the leading cause of falls in adults.
这是成人摔倒的主要原因
Currently, fall risk is assessed by a care provider
目前摔倒风险是由保健服务提供者
through a questionnaire and an in-person evaluation.
通过问卷和现场评估方式来实现
But this can miss out on your everyday movement,
但遗漏了日常运动因素
so important changes can go unnoticed.
可能会忽视重要的变化
Your iPhone already captures mobility data as you walk
iPhone 根据经科学验证的指标
with scientifically validated metrics.
捕捉了你行走时的移动数据
We're building on this to introduce
我们在此基础上推出
a completely new way to assess your risk of falling
评估摔倒风险的全新方式
called Walking Steadiness.
步行稳定性
For the first time ever,
这是有史以来第一次
you can get insight if your fall risk increases
你将了解到自己的摔倒风险是否增加
and take action early to improve your steadiness.
以便尽早采取措施改善你的稳定性
Let's take a quick look at some of the science behind this.
我们快速看下背后的一些科学原理
As you walk with your iPhone, the built-in motion sensors
携带 iPhone 行走时， 手机内置运动传感器
automatically measure how fast and how evenly you walk,
会自动测量行走速度和均匀度
the length of your steps, and the timing of each step,
步长、每步用时
right down to how often you have both feet on the ground.
乃至你双脚着地的时间
Combined, these metrics provide powerful insight
综合分析这些指标 就能洞悉
on changes in your balance, stability, and coordination.
你的平衡性、稳定性和协调性变化
We used real-world data
我们运用
from the Apple Heart & Movement Study,
Apple Heart & Movement Study 的真实数据
with over 100,000 participants across all ages.
各年龄段共有10 万多人参与这项研究
This is the largest data set ever used to study fall risk,
这是迄今规模最大的摔倒风险研究数据集
and it's helped create this first of its kind health metric.
帮助创建了这鲮鱼首个健康指标
You can view your Walking Steadiness in the Health app.
你可在健康 app 中查看 步行稳定性
You'll see a classification of "OK"
如果各项指标显示你行走时是稳定的
if the metrics show that you're stable while walking.
步行稳定性 会显示“OK”
You can see how your Walking Steadiness
你可以看到步行稳定性
may change as the months go by
逐月变化趋势
and receive a notification if your steadiness is low
如果你的稳定行较低
or very low and you're at increased risk of falling.
或很低且摔倒的风险增加时，你会收到通知
You can also learn how to improve your steadiness.
你还可以了解如何改善你的稳定性
There are movement exercises right in the Health app,
健康 app 中就有相关运动锻炼
and these can help you increase your strength and balance
帮助你增强力量和平衡能力
and reduce your risk of falling.
降低摔倒风险
Now back to Sumbul
下面有请 Sumbul
to tell you about another way to monitor health changes.
为你介绍监测健康变化的另一种方式
[Sumbul] You can already review lab results
你的化验结果
like your cholesterol right in the Health app.
例如胆固醇等，可以在健康 app 中查看
In the U.S. alone, 14 billion clinical laboratory tests
仅美国 每年就有 140 亿次临床化验
are performed each year.
进行
That is a lot of information to keep track of.
这需要跟踪大量信息
When you see your own results come in,
拿到自己的化验结果
it can be hard to understand what these tests mean
你可能不理解这些测试意味着什么
or what has changed.
或不清楚有哪些变化
The Health app will now include detailed descriptions
健康 app 会显示详细说明
to help you better understand your lab data.
助于你更好了解自己的化验数据
For example, when you receive a cholesterol result,
比如 收到胆固醇化验结果时
you can now see that the LDL is a bad cholesterol
你会知道低密度脂蛋白是一种有害的胆固醇
and having too much may put you at risk for heart disease.
积聚过多 可能有患心脏病的风险
You can also now see whether your labs
你还能查看化验结果
are within expected ranges.
是否在预期范围内
Together, these views will help you
综合分析这些视图将帮助你
get even more meaning from your lab results.
深入了解化验结果
Many health changes happen over time,
许多健康变化是日积月累的
so to better understand your health
为了更为充分全面
even more holistically, we're introducing Trends.
趋势
You'll get insight on long-term changes
你将深入了解长期变化
across areas such as steps, resting heart rate,
例如步数、静息心率
blood glucose, sleep, and much more.
血糖、睡眠等方面
You'll also be alerted when there's a new trend
当数据有新趋势时，你会收到提醒
in your data, which may be something
在你的数据中有
you want to monitor more closely
哪些指标需要密切监测
or even discuss with your physician.
甚至与医生讨论
So if you're getting more daily walks in,
如果你每天有更多的步行
your health summary will show
健康摘要将显示
that your steps taken have increased
过去几个月
over the last few months.
步数在增加
This is a great way to celebrate progress
这是庆祝你实现健康目标的进度
towards meeting your health goals
的最佳方式
and a powerful new way to get early insight
这是一种很有效的方法，可以让我们更早地了解
into potential health issues.
潜在的新健康问题
With Trends, Walking Steadiness,
有了趋势、步行稳定性 Walking Steadiness
and a better Labs experience,
和更好的 Labs 体验
you have three new ways to see changes
你有三种全新的方式来了解自己
in your overall health.
整体健康的变化
Another really important part of managing your health
管理健康的另一重要环节是
is having meaningful conversations with your doctor.
与医生进行有意义的交谈
During your visit, physicians look at your vitals and labs
就诊期间 医生会查看主要体征和化验结果
but will also ask you about everyday health activities
也会询问日常健康活动
like exercise and sleep.
比如锻炼和睡眠
And patients can often have difficulty
病人往往难以
remembering all these details.
记住所有详尽数据
But the Health app has all of this valuable information,
但健康 app 存有全部重要信息
so, to support this conversation,
所以 为支持此类交谈
you can now share health data that you choose
你可以选定健康数据
with your healthcare provider in a private way.
以私密的方式 与保建提供者分享
For example, if you have a concern about your heart health,
比如 如果担忧心脏健康
you can now share your heart data.
你可分享心脏数据
This is shared securely.
这是安全共享的
No one else, including Apple, will see this information.
任何人，包括 Apple 都看不到这些信息
Your doctor can then view this data directly
医生可从电子健康档案系统中
from their electronic health record system
直接查看这些数据
and look for important trends such as changes in activity
寻找重要趋势 比如活动变化
and a history of alerts like high heart rate.
心率过高等提醒的历史记录
Access to this information helps give your doctor
访问这些信息能助于医生
a more complete view of your everyday health
更全面了解你在诊所之外的
outside of the clinic.
日常健康状况
We're so excited about this new capability
我们对这项新功能感到非常兴奋
to share your data from the Health app
能将健康 app 中的数据
directly with your doctor.
直接分享给你的医生
These electronic health record companies in the U.S.
美国的这些电子健康档案公司
will be the first to support this feature,
将率先支持这功能
and we look forward to expanding availability
未来几个月
even more in the coming months.
我们有望进一步扩大使用范围
Now, for many of us, it's not just the changes
对于许多用户来说
in our own health we care about.
我们不单注重自己的健康变化
It's the health of our family and loved ones too,
不管他们是和我们住在一起还是住得很远
whether they live with us or far away.
无论是同住屋檐下 还是相隔一方
For some of us, that means taking care of our kids
有些用户 要照料孩子
and for others, it's our aging parents.
还有些用户 要服侍年迈父母
And for many of us,
对于许多用户来说
it's actually taking care of both--
都要悉心照顾
generations above and below.
上一代和下一代
To empower you to care for others,
为了让你有能力照顾他人
we're introducing Health Sharing,
我们推出健康共享
a private and secure way to view health data,
以私密安全的方式查看
trends, and alerts for the people most important to you.
对你最重要的人的健康数据、趋势和提醒
For example, I could set up a sharing relationship
比如 我能与母亲建立共享关系
with my mom, and with her permission,
获得她允许之后
I could view data like her heart rate,
我就能查看她的数据，例如心率
activity, and labs.
活动、化验信息等数据
And just like with my own health data,
就像我自己的健康数据一样
Trends proactively highlights changes in my Mom's health data
趋势主动为我凸显我母亲健康数据的
for me.
变化
I can also receive notifications,
我还可以收到通知
including high heart rate alerts,
包括高心率提醒
changes in mobility, and more.
活动能力变化等
And it's easy for me to connect with her about her health.
方便同她沟通她的健康问题
So if I see a noteworthy change
如果我发现需要注意的变化
like her resting heart rate increasing,
比如她的静息心率加快
I can simply tap Messages
我只需轻点“信息”
and start a conversation with my mom.
即可与母亲开始交谈
This is a powerful new way to stay connected
这是一种关注你所爱的人的健康
to the wellbeing of those you love.
的强大方式
You'll have peace of mind,
你会感到心安
and they'll know they have a trusted partner
而他们也知道在他们健康之旅中
on their health journey.
有个信赖的伙伴
Since the beginning of our work in Health,
从设计健康 app 伊始
all of our health features have been architected
所有健康功能的构建
to keep your data secure and protect your privacy.
都是为了保证数据安全和保护隐私
Your health data is under your control
你的健康数据在你的掌控之下
and is encrypted in transit and at rest.
在传输和存储时是加密的
The permissions built into the sharing experience
共享体验加入许可功能
give you granular control
便于你精细控制
over which types of data you share and with whom.
数据共享类型和对象
And you can make changes at any time
你可以在“共享”标签页
right from the Sharing tab.
随时作改动
Data you share is sent in an encrypted form,
共享的数据以加密形式发送
and Apple does not have access to any of this information.
Apple 无法访问其中任何信息
Privacy is fundamental in the design and development
设计和开发所有“健康”功能时
across all of our Health features.
一切以隐私为基础
We're so excited for what's coming in Health--
我们为即将到来的健康功能感到兴奋，
a first-of-its-kind metric to access fall risk,
针对摔倒风险评估的指标
richer insights to understand changes in your health,
全新的功能让你
and completely new abilities for you to privately share
全新隐私的方式
selected data with your doctors and loved ones.
以选定的数据分享给医生和你所爱的人
Now I'll hand it over to Kevin to talk about watchOS.
下面有请 Kevin 介绍 watchOS
[Kevin] Apple Watch is already
Apple Watch 是最受世人喜爱的手表
With features like Fall Detection,
凭借摔倒检测 心电图
ECG, and Cycle Tracking,
心电图、经期跟踪等功能
Apple Watch is an essential health companion.
Apple Watch 实属不可或缺的健康伴侣
It motivates you to close your Activity rings
不单激励你填满活动圆环
and transforms the way you stay fit.
更转变你保持健康的方式
And staying connected to the people and things
与你最在乎的人和事保持联系
you care about most is easy with Apple Watch--
在 Apple Watch 上容易实现
all from your wrist.
都在你手腕上
In watchOS 8, we're introducing more capabilities
在 watchOS 8, 我们针对这些领域
in each of these areas.
推出更多功能
Let's start with health.
先来看健康
More than ever, people are realizing
大家比以往更意识到
the importance of dedicating time to practice mindfulness.
抽时间训练正念的重要性
In fact, the Breathe app has grown in popularity,
其实 呼吸 app 日益受欢迎
particularly over this last year.
尤其是在去年
In watchOS 8, the Breathe app has been enhanced
在 watchOS 8，呼吸 app 的功能以增强
to give you more opportunities
给你更多机会
to slow down and be mindful, including a new animation
慢下来和留意 同时启用全新
that has a beautiful look and feel
精美动画
to help you center and calm as you breathe.
帮助你一边呼吸 一边集中和平静
We're also introducing Reflect--
我们还将推出沉思
a new way for you to be more mindful.
一种有助于更加专注的新方式
For example, a reflection could be
比如 反思可以是
"Think about something you love to do
“思考你喜爱做的事情
and why it brings you joy."
及让你感到快乐的原因“
A gentle animation helps you focus.
舒缓的动画助于专注
And studies show that regular mindful moments like this
研究表明经常像这样训练正念
can lead to increased positive emotions
有助于增强积极的情绪
and overall psychological well-being.
和整体心理健康度
The Reflect and Breathe sessions live in the new Mindfulness app.
全新 正念训练 app 分为沉思和呼吸两部分
This will help you reduce stress and relax your body and mind.
这将帮助你减少压力 放松身心
With the Sleep app,
在睡眠 app里
we introduced an entirely new way
我们推出全新的方式
for you to meet your sleep goals
帮助你达到睡眠目标
and track metrics like time asleep,
跟踪睡眠指标，例如睡眠时长
heart rate, and even blood oxygen.
心率、甚至血氧
In watchOS 8,
在 watchOS 8 中
Apple Watch can track another key metric
Apple Watch 可以跟踪睡眠时的
while sleeping--
另一项关键指标
Respiratory Rate.
呼吸速率
This is a vital sign that measures
这一个主要体征衡量
how many breaths you take per minute.
每分钟的呼吸次数
And since your sleeping respiratory rate
由于你的睡眠呼吸速率逐渐趋于稳定
tends to be consistent over time,
呼吸速率的变化可能
a change may indicate a shift in your overall wellness.
表明整体健康状况可能有所变化
You'll be notified if a meaningful trend
如果在呼吸速率发现了
in your respiratory rate has been identified.
有意义的趋势 你会收到通知
And you can see even more details
你在健康 app 中还能看到
in Respiratory Rate in the Health app.
呼吸速率的更多细节
Now I'd like to turn it over to Julz
下面有请 Julz 为你介绍
to tell you what's coming to help you stay active.
有助于保持活跃的新功能
[Julz] Apple Watch is the perfect companion
Apple Watch 是激励你
to motivate you to be more fit.
愈发健康的完美伴侣
And watchOS 8 adds two of the most popular workout types
watchOS 8 新增两种热门体能训练
that are great for bringing more mindful movement
有益于为日常生活带来
to your routine.
更需意念的运动
First, a new Tai Chi workout.
第一个是太极
This Chinese martial art is thousands of years old
这一中国武术有数千年历史
and is often described as meditation in motion.
被誉为“运动中的冥想”
Its gentle approach can help reduce stress
其动作轻缓 有助于减压
and find a more peaceful state of mind.
和保持更为平和的心境
And a brand-new Pilates workout type,
而全新的普拉提训练
which is one of the best ways to develop core strength,
是开发中枢肌肉力量
posture, balance, and flexibility.
姿势、平衡和柔韧性的一种最佳方式
Of course, another way people are staying fit
当然 用户保持健康的另一种方式
is with Apple Fitness+,
是使用 Apple Fitness+
the first service built entirely around Apple Watch.
这是完全围绕 Apple Watch 打造的首项服务
We've heard from so many of our users
许多用户表示 Fitness+
how it's making a positive difference in their lives.
为生活带来积极改变
And now, Fitness+ is introducing a new series of workouts
Fitness+ 将推出一套全新体能训练系列
featuring Jeanette Jenkins,
由Jeanette Jenkins 领衔
one of the most sought after fitness experts.
最受欢迎的健身专家之一
With seven workouts focused on Strength
通过七套力量
and High Intensity Interval Training,
和高强度间歇训练
she's bringing the fire
她点燃运动热情
and her belief that all bodies are made to be strong.
推崇身体都是强壮的理念
Because music is so key to the Fitness+ experience,
音乐在 Fitness+ 体验中发挥着重要作用
we're introducing a new Artist Spotlight Series.
因此 我们将推出全新 Artist Spotlight Series
Each workout features an entire playlist
每套体能训练主打一整份歌单
from Lady Gaga, Jennifer Lopez,
精选自 Lady Gaga、Jennifer Lopez
Keith Urban, and Alicia Keys.
Keith Urban、Alicia Keys
The Artist Spotlight Series and the new workouts with Jeanette
The Artist Spotlight Series 及 Jeanette 领衔的全新体能训练
will be available later this month.
将于本月晚些时候推出
With new workout types and great new Fitness+ content,
凭借新增的体能训练项目和 Fitness+ 出色的全新内容
Apple Watch continues to be an incredible motivator
Apple Watch 将继续以精彩纷呈的方式
to help you stay active and fit.
激励你保持活跃和健康
Back to you, Kevin.
交还给你 Kevin
[Kevin] Let's talk about some new features
我们来聊下一些帮助你与
to keep you connected to the people you love.
你所爱的人保持联系的新功能
Photos are a great way to relive your favorite moments
照片让你温你最喜欢的时刻
and most precious memories.
和最珍贵的回忆
On Apples Watch, the Photos face
照片表盘是 Apples Watch 上
is the most popular Watch face.
最受欢迎的表盘
That's why watchOS 8 is bringing another great way
因此 watchOS 8 将推出
to enjoy your favorite photos
另一种欣赏心仪照片的巧妙方式
with the new Portraits Watch face.
全新人像表盘
It takes the great portrait photos from your iPhone
其从 iPhone 中精选人像照片
and uses the segmentation data
利用人像图割数据
to create a multi-layered face with depth.
创建具有景深的多图层表盘
And you can make this watch face your own
你还可以自定义表盘
by adjusting the photo's composition and time placement
调节照片构图和时间设置
to really make the subject stand out.
突出主题
This is really great to see live,
百闻不如一见
so let me invite Shandra to show you a demo.
下面有请 Shandra 为你演示
[Shandra] Thanks, Kevin.
谢谢 Kevin
Your photo comes to life when you raise your wrist.
抬起手腕 就会显示照片
And as you scroll the digital crown,
滚动数码表冠
you get a view of the dynamic composition
即可查看动态构图
that makes this watch face extraordinary.
令这款表盘卓尔不凡
You're gonna love how this face keeps you connected
无法见面时
when you can't be face-to-face.
可以时不时看到你想念的人
Speaking of photos,
谈到照片
the Photos app itself has been completely redesigned.
照片 app 经彻底重新设计
It now includes memory highlights,
除了个人收藏 ，还新增了精选回忆
featured photos, in addition to your favorites.
和精选照片
If I tap into this memory,
我轻点这个记忆后
I can scroll through the all-new mosaic layout.
可以滚动浏览这全新马赛克排布的照片布局
My daughter Wesleigh and I
我女儿 Wesleigh 和我
adopted our puppy Fondue last year
去年收养了小狗 Fondue
and are missing her during the day.
我们白天都很想她
The new Photos app makes it simple for us
全新照片 app 便于我们
to quickly reminisce.
快速追忆往事
This picture from my Memories is a good one.
我好喜欢回忆中的这张照片
I'm gonna share it with Wesleigh to remind her
我想与 Wesleigh 共享
we're not always missing Fondue's best moments.
让她知道我们不是总错过 Fondue 的精彩时刻
If I tap the share icon,
轻点共享图标
you'll see that we now have support for sharing photos
即可通过信息和邮件 app
via messages and mail, directly from my Watch.
直接发送手表上的共享照片
Let's get this over to Wesleigh.
我们发条信息给 Wesleigh
I'm gonna tap add message to show you
我将轻点添加信息 让你看到
that we've made it even easier to compose a message.
编写信息变得更方便了
We can now dictate, Scribble,
可在同一视图内 听写、随手写
and add emojis in the same view.
和添加表情符号
I always find it easy to dictate my messages.
我总觉得用听写功能编写信息很方便
Remember this?
记得这个吗？
If I tap Scribble, I can edit my text inline
轻点随手写 即可字间编辑文字
by selecting and deleting what I'd like to change.
选择想更改的文本并删除
And I can use the crown to move the cursor
旋转表冠 移动光标
and add additional text.
再添加文字
And what message is complete without emojis
发信息不用表情符号
to get a point across?
无法完整表达观点
By tapping the emoji icon, I can add multiple emojis
轻点“表情符号”图标 即可在随手写视图中
while in the Scribble view.
添加多个表情符号
watchOS 8 makes it easy to send the perfect message
watchOS 8 让你轻松发送完美信息
right from your wrist.
就从你手腕上实现
[chime] That was quick.
速度很快
Wesleigh must have the puppy on the brain too.
Wesleigh 必定也在想小狗了
And with GIFs now on Apple Watch,
Apple Watch 现支持 GIF 动图
I can reply as comedically as I would from my iPhone.
我能像使用 iPhone 一样搞笑回复
In the new app shelf, you'll find #images.
全新 App 架 陈列 #images
You can search for the perfect GIF
你可搜索完美 GIF 动图
or choose from your recents.
或从最近图库中选取
I think a face palm best captures
我觉得这张捂脸动图
how this photo makes me feel.
最能表达我当前的感受
And that's a look at what's coming in watchOS 8
这就是 watchOS 8 中便于你
to keep you connected to the people
与你关怀的人和小狗
and puppies you care about most.
保持联系的全新功能
And now, back to Kevin.
接下来，交还给 Kevin
[Kevin] We think you're gonna love these new features
希望你喜欢照片和信息 app 中的
in Photos and Messages.
这些全新功能
And of course, there's so much more,
当然 除此之外
including Next Hour Precipitation,
还有未来一个小时降水
support for Find Items, and Multiple Timers.
查找物品支持和
watchOS is the world's most advanced
watchOS 是当今最先进的
wearable operating system.
可穿戴操作系统
And watchOS 8 takes it even further
watchOS 8 更进一步
with new features to help you stay healthy,
推出全新功能 帮助你保持健康
active, and connected.
活跃和联系
And now, over to Craig.
接下来，交给 Craig
[Craig] Let's talk about the home.
我们聊下家庭场景
At Apple, we design our products for the home
在 Apple 我们设计家庭产品时
to embody three key attributes
体现三大关键属性
starting with being easy to use.
首先是易于使用
We believe the technology in your home
我们认为 家庭采用的技术
should work for you, not the other way around.
应服务于你 而不是你迁就技术
And we design our products to work better together
我们设计的产品能充分发挥协同效应
so that your iPhone, HomePod mini,
你的 iPhone、HomePod mini
Apple TV, and other devices
Apple TV 和其他设备
can leverage each other to deliver seamless experiences.
能相互配合 共同塑造无缝使用体验
And everything we do is built to be private and secure,
我们所做的一切均以隐私和安全为重
which is so important to all of us.
这对所有用户都至关重要
With this foundation, we have a great set of features
在此基础上 我们将于今年
coming this year to make life at home more enjoyable.
推出一系列优秀功能 令家庭生活更有乐趣
To tell you more, here's Yah.
下面有请 Yah 为你详细介绍
At the heart of your smart home is HomeKit,
智能家居的核心是 HomeKit
seamlessly orchestrating and controlling
无缝协调和控制
your smart home accessories.
智能家居配件
And it all starts at your front door.
一切始于正门
With our new Home Keys feature,
全新家庭钥匙功能推出之后
simply tap your iPhone or Apple Watch
只需用 iPhone 或 Apple Watch 轻触
to securely unlock the door, just like that.
即可安全打开门锁 就像这样
Now, sometimes when you get home,
有时你回到家
you just can't wait to watch your favorite show,
迫不及待想看心仪的节目
so we've made that easier than ever.
现在更方便了
Starting this fall, you can ask Siri on HomePod mini
今秋起 你可以唤醒 HomePod mini 上的 Siri
to play something on your Apple TV--
要求在 Apple TV 上播放内容
completely hands-free.
完全摆脱手动操作
[mom] Hey, Siri, watch the latest episode
嘿 Siri 观看最新一集
of Mosquito Coast.
Mosquito Coast
[Yah] For many of us, the only thing better than watching TV
对于许多用户而言
is watching TV with friends.
与朋友一起看电视最开心
As you heard from Craig earlier,
如 Craig 此前所述
SharePlay is going to change the way you enjoy TV together.
SharePlay 将改变一起看电视的方式
You can watch it all on Apple TV,
你可在 Apple TV 上独赏
in sync with your friends on FaceTime,
也可邀朋友在 FaceTime 上共赏
ensuring everyone catches the movie's dramatic reveal
确保大家同赏电影大结局
or a show's punchline at the same moment.
或电视节目笑点
And to make it easier to see everything
为方便欣赏
your friends are talking about,
朋友讨论的所有情节
the Apple TV app will now feature a new
Apple TV app 将推出全新
"Shared with You" row,
与你共享栏目
highlighting all the great shows and movies
突出显示朋友在信息 app 上
your friends are sharing in Messages.
共享的所有精彩节目和影片
We also want to make it easier to decide
我们还希望方便
what to watch as a group,
一家人在一起时的选片
especially if Mom's into action movies,
特别是如果妈妈喜欢看动作片
Grandma loves sci-fi,
奶奶喜欢看科幻片
and the teens can't get enough of comedy.
青少年超爱看喜剧片
That's why we're introducing a new row called
因此 我们推出全新栏目
"For All of You," with a collection of shows
For All of You
and movies based on everyone's interests--
展示一系列节目和电影
perfect for family movie nights.
适合全家共度电影之夜
And you can easily fine tune the suggestions
你可根据观看对象
based on who's watching.
轻松微调视频推荐
Now, when you're ready to watch something,
当你准备好观看视频内容的时候
you want it to sound amazing.
你希望视频里的声音也要很震撼
So this fall, you can select HomePod mini
今秋 你可选择 HomePod mini
as the speakers for your Apple TV 4K.
作为 Apple TV 4K 的扬声器
With the power of Computational Audio,
得益于计算音频
HomePod mini delivers rich, balanced sound
HomePod mini 的声音平衡且有层次
and crystal-clear dialogue for everything you watch.
对话清晰剔透 与所有画面相得益彰
[Yah] HomePod mini is perfect for any room,
HomePod mini 适合任何房间
like the Kitchen, where you can convert measurements,
比如厨房 你可以转换测量值
set a timer, or add to your grocery list.
设置计时器或添加物品到购物清单
Of course, you can always listen to Apple music
当然 你可随时聆听 Apple Music
and other popular music services.
和其他热门音乐服务
And we're excited to add support
令人高兴的是
for lossless audio, Apple Music, later this year.
今年晚些时候 Apple Music 将增加对无损音频的支持
Because we want more people
因为 我们希望有更多用户
to experience the magic of HomePod mini,
体验 HomePod mini 的魔力
we're now making it available in even more countries and regions.
HomePod mini 将在更多国家和地区推出
In addition to everywhere we ship HomePod mini today,
除了当前有售卖的市场
we're bringing it to Austria,
HomePod mini 将于本月
Ireland, and New Zealand this month.
登陆奥地利、爱尔兰和新西兰
And it'll be available in Italy by the end of the year.
今年底 将在意大利市场发售
Also later this year,
今年晚些时候
we'll begin bringing voice recognition
在发售 HomePod mini 的各大市场
everywhere HomePod mini ships,
将推出声音识别功能
giving each member of the home a personalized experience.
为每位家庭成员奉上个性化体验
So each person can ask Siri to send a message,
大家都可以要求 Siri 发送信息
set their own reminders,
设置他们自己的提醒事项
or hear a playlist curated just for them.
或者聆听为他们精心编排的歌单
We believe Siri is most powerful
我们认为 当 Siri 在你家中的每一个地方都可以被触及的时候
when it's available throughout your house,
将发挥最大威力
which is why we're so excited
因此 我们很高兴
to bring Siri to third-party devices.
为第三方设备带来 Siri
For the first time, HomeKit accessory makers
HomeKit 配件制造商将首次
can enable Siri in their products,
可以在自己的产品中启用 Siri
so you'll be able to talk with Siri
你将能在更多设备上
on even more devices.
与 Siri 交谈
[grandma] Hey, Siri, set the Dinner scene.
嘿 Siri, 设置晚餐场景
[Yah] We've designed it so that your Siri requests
按设计要求 Siri 请求
flow to your HomePod
只会传输至 HomePod
without going to any third-party servers,
不会流向任何第三方服务器
providing the privacy you expect from Apple.
提供你期待 Apple 所能实现的隐私保护功能
Accessories enabled with Siri
支持 Siri 的配件
will be available starting later this year.
将于今年晚些时候开始发售
And, to make your smart home accessories
同时 为了让智能家居配件
work together seamlessly, we formed an alliance
无缝协同工作 我们携手多家行业领导者
with other industry leaders
共同组建了一个联盟
to create a new smart home interoperability standard
制定全新智能家居互用性标准
called Matter.
Matter
It leverages the HomeKit technology
它借鉴了去年开源的
we open-sourced last year,
HomeKit 技术
and we're excited to announce
我们欣喜宣布
that support is coming in iOS 15.
iOS 15 将支持这一技术
You can control HomeKit and Matter-enabled accessories
你可使用家庭 app 控制 HomeKit 配件
with the Home app.
和支持 Matter 标准的配件
and this year, we're making it even better
今年 Apple Watch 上的家庭 app
on Apple Watch.
将更为完善
You can tap Intercom to broadcast a message
你可以轻点广播功能来传话。
you're most likely to need in that moment.
急需使用的配件
You can even see what's going on around the house.
你甚至能看到全屋的情况
With the HomeKit-enabled doorbell,
有了支持 HomeKit 的门铃
it's easy to see who's at the door
在 Apple Watch 上就可以看到
and greet them right from your wrist.
谁在门口并表示欢迎
HomeKit Secure Video uses the on-device intelligence
HomeKit 安全视频运用 Apple TV
of your Apple TV or HomePod mini
或 HomePod mini 设备端的智能技术
to alert you when people, animals, or vehicles
当检测到人、动物或车辆时
are detected.
会发出提示
And this year, we're adding Package Detection
今年 我们将增加包裹检测功能
so you know when a package has arrived.
包裹送达时 你将收到通知
And we're adding new ways
我们还将增加
to take advantage of your cameras on Apple TV.
Apple TV 中调用摄像头的全新使用方式
While viewing a camera,
查看摄像头时
you'll now be able to control nearby accessories
你将能控制附近的配件
such as turning on the outdoor lights.
比如打开室外灯
And you can even display multiple cameras
甚至可以同时显示
at the same time, giving you a more complete view
多个摄像头的画面
of what's happening around the house.
更为全面了解全屋的情况
Those are just some of the great experiences
这就是我们今秋为
we're bringing to the home this fall.
家庭带来的部分精彩体验
With incredible new features like Home Keys,
凭借超群的新功能 比如家庭钥匙
SharePlay for shared viewing,
适合共赏的 SharePlay
and access to Siri in more places than ever before,
更多 Siri 使用场景
your smart home has never been more capable.
智能家居从未如此全能
Back to Craig.
把镜头交还给 Craig
[Craig] Let's talk about macOS.
我们聊一下 macOS
macOS has always been about the fusion of power and simplicity.
macOS 始终崇尚性能和简约兼具
And with our current release,
当前版本
macOS Big Sur, we introduced a bold new design
macOS Big Sur 推出了大胆的全新设计
that gives users more control and huge updates for apps--
赋予用户更多控制权和 app 的大幅更新
all while making everything easier to use.
同时令一切功能更易使用
And when combined with the M1 chip,
结合 M1 芯片
Big Sur delivers unmatched levels of performance
Big Sur 带来无可匹敌的性能
and battery life.
和电池续航时间
With people using the Mac more than ever,
Mac 日益普及之际
macOS has become an even bigger part of our daily lives.
macOS 在日常生活中愈加举足轻重
And our next release is focused on helping you
下一版本侧重于帮助你
do even more.
完成更多任务
But what should we call it?
但我们应该怎样命名这个新版本？
Well, that brings us to the latest exploits
那要归功于
of our crack marketing team.
我们优秀的营销团队
With their annual vision quest postponed,
由于年度灵感寻找活动被推迟后
our merry band of nomadic namers
这群快乐的游牧起名人
wandered aimlessly through the California hills
漫无目的游荡于加州丘陵
before donning their technicolor wet suits
又穿上色彩绚丽的潜水服
and immersing themselves in the inspiration
沉浸于 Monterey 缤纷水域
of the beautiful, rich waters of Monterey.
带来的灵感中无法自拔
macOS Monterey gives you the power
macOS Monterey
to accomplish more than ever
能助你胜任更多任务
and helps you work fluidly across all your devices.
并帮助你跨所有设备顺畅工作
The incredible features we talked about earlier
我们前面提到的出众功能
are going to be great for the ways you work on Mac,
十分有助于你在 Mac 上工作
like the new capabilities in FaceTime
比如 FaceTime 的新功能
which help you look and sound your best
你在与同事好友交谈时
while talking to coworkers or friends.
帮助你保持最佳形象和声音
With SharePlay, it's just plain awesome
开启 SharePlay
to watch movies and shows together
在惊艳的 Mac 显示屏上
on your stunning Mac display
一起观看电影和节目
or share an app window as you collaborate on a project.
或项目合作时共享 app 窗口
Shared with You offers a totally new way
与你共享以全新方式
to discover photos, articles and more
在 Mac app 中探索其他用户
that people share with you over Messages
在信息 app 上与你共享的
right in your Mac apps.
照片和文章等
And when you're working hard on a Mac,
在 Mac 上埋头工作时
you can choose a Focus that syncs across all your devices,
你可选择一个跨所有设备同步的专注模式
helping reduce distracting notifications
这有助于减少通知干扰
so you can get the job done.
以便顺利完成工作
Plus, Quick Note and Notes
此外快速备忘录和备忘录 app
give you versatile new ways to capture
赋予你捕捉和组织思路的
and organize your thoughts.
很多新方式
These powerful features are just fantastic on the Mac.
这些强大的功能在 Mac 上让用户获得非凡的体验
And we have even more new features
我们还有许多全新功能
that make it easier to work across all your devices,
令跨设备工作更轻松
starting with Continuity.
首先介绍连续互通
Every device we make is powerful in its own way,
我们制造的每一种设备都在各自的领域性能强大
and when you use them together
当一起使用这些设备时
you unlock new experiences that feel truly magical.
便会解锁全新的神奇体验
This year, we've created a completely new way
今年 我们开创了一种全新方式
to work across your devices
以更高精准度
with greater precision and speed, and we call it--
和更快速度跨设备工作 我们称之为
Universal Control.
Universal Control
With Universal Control,
有了 Universal Control
you can now use a single mouse and keyboard
只用一套鼠标和键盘
to move between your Mac and iPad
即可在 Mac 和 iPad 之间移动
for a seamless experience.
享受无缝操作体验
Universal Control is so incredible,
Universal Control 是如此出色
you just have to see it in action.
必须亲眼所见
Let me show it to you now.
让我来为你演示
I'm putting the final touches on an illustration
我正在 iPad 上对一幅插图
here on my iPad.
作最后润色
It's the last piece I need to finish a presentation
添上最后这幅插图
that I have open on my MacBook.
就可以完成这个在 MacBook 上打开的的演示文稿
Now, I'll just set my iPad down next to my Mac,
我现在把 iPad 放到 Mac 旁边
and check this out.
请注意
Without any other setup,
无需其他任何设置
I'm gonna simply move my Mac cursor
只需将 Mac 上的光标
towards my iPad,
移向 iPad
and the iPad automatically recognizes it.
iPad 就能自动识别光标
And if I move a bit further,
如果我再移一点
boom--my cursor is now on the iPad.
光标就会出现在 iPad 上
How cool is that?
是不是很神奇？
And now I can move my cursor back and forth effortlessly
我可以在两台设备之间
between the two.
来回移动光标 毫不费力
Now, it's easy to control my iPad
只需使用 Mac 的键盘和触控板
with just the keyboard and trackpad on my Mac.
即可轻松控制 iPad
For instance, I can click and close this document,
比如我可以点击并关闭这篇文稿
and flick on my trackpad
或在触控板上向上滑动
to return to my iPad home screen.
返回 iPad 主屏幕
And of course, I can swipe between my pages of apps,
当然 我可以轻扫切换 app 页面
And I can use my MacBook's keyboard
我还可以使用 MacBook 的键盘
to open Spotlight and, say, launch Notes.
打开聚焦搜索 输入“备忘录” 从而启动备忘录 app
And I can even use command-tab
我还可以使用 command-tab 组合键
to switch right back to Procreate.
切换回 Procreate
This is really powerful.
功能极为强大
With Universal Control,
有了 Universal Control
I can even drag and drop files between my devices.
我还能在设备之间拖拽文件
I'm just gonna take this drawing I finished on my iPad
我要把刚在 iPad 上画好的这幅画
and drop it into my Keynote on my Mac.
拖到 Mac 上的 Keynote 中
Awesome.
棒极了
For our pros out there,
对于专业人士
Universal Control works with more than two devices.
Universal Control 适用于两台以上设备
So let's add this iMac to the mix.
我们把这台 iMac 加入组合
Now I can use the trackpad on my MacBook
我还可以用 MacBook 上的
to control my iMac as well.
触控板控制 iMac
I can also switch to my iMac's keyboard and mouse.
我还可以切换到 iMac 的键盘和鼠标
This is so cool. Watch this.
这个功能很酷 请看
Now, I have a title text image I've been working on here
我一直在 iPad 的 Procreate 中
in Procreate on my iPad.
画一幅标题文本图像
Now I'm gonna take this image
我要把这张图像
and drag it across all three devices
拖动经过所有三台设备
and drop it into FinalCut.
拖入 FinalCut
Just like that.
就像这样
Let's see the final product.
我们来看成品
Nice.
效果很好
That's a quick look at Universal Control
我们快览了 macOS Monterey 上的
on macOS Monterey.
Universal Control
Universal Control makes it effortless
Universal Control 可以让用户在
to move between your devices
设备之间轻松切换
so you can be more productive and focus your energy
不单可以提高工作效率 还可以集中精力
on the task at hand.
做好手头的工作
Another way our devices work great together
多台设备协同配合的优势
is with AirPlay.
亦体现于隔空播放
We all love the way AirPlay lets us watch a movie
大家都喜爱隔空播放将 iPhone 的画面
or share a presentation
投射到电视上 我们就能
from your iPhone to a TV just like that.
观看电影或共享演示文稿 就像这样
But there's another screen with its stunning Retina display
但还有一块屏幕拥有惊艳的
that makes everything you watch simply amazing.
视网膜显示屏 它令你的所有观看都变得惊艳
That's why we're introducing
所以 我们将推出
AirPlay to Mac.
隔空播放到 Mac
It works just like AirPlay today,
工作方式就像现在的隔空播放
so it's instantly familiar.
立马能上手
You can play, present, and share just about anything.
你可以播放、演示和共享几乎任何内容
As you draw a sketch on iPad,
你在 iPad 上画草图时
your colleagues can follow along on the bigger display.
同事就能在大屏上观看你怎么画
And you can even take advantage of any Mac's high-fidelity sound
你还可利用任何 Mac 的高保真音响
by using it as an AirPlay speaker.
作为隔空播放扬声器
AirPlay brings your Mac to life in whole new ways.
隔空播放以全新方式令 Mac 焕发生机
With macOS Monterey,
有了 macOS Monterey
your devices work together like never before,
你的多个 Apple 设备将以前所未有的方式协同工作
making it more fluid to work across them.
便于跨设备更顺畅工作
And we're not just reinventing how you work between devices.
我们不单重塑你在设备之间的工作方式
We're also giving you powerful new tools
我们还推出强大的全新工具
to get more work done on your devices.
帮助你在设备上完成更多工作
The Mac has a long, deep history of automation
Mac 一直以命令行
with Command line, shell scripts,
Shell 脚本、AppleScript
AppleScript, and Automator.
和自动操作实现自动化
And on iOS, we've made automation even easier
在 iOS 上 我们使用快捷指令
with Shortcuts.
轻松实现自动化
Shortcuts takes all the taps and swipes you usually need
快捷指令可以组合通常所需的轻点和轻扫操作
to order your favorite lunch
自动帮你订购心仪午餐
and makes it as simple as tapping a button
你只需要轻点按钮或呼唤 Siri 就可以触发快捷指令
or asking Siri.
非常简单
Shortcuts is all about helping you get more done--
快捷指令旨在帮助你以更快速度
faster.
完成更多任务
Because you can let your device do the work for you.
因为你可以让设备为你工作
And this year, we're bringing Shortcuts to the Mac.
今年 Mac 将迎来快捷指令
The Mac is, after all,
Mac 毕竟是
where we turn for so much of our creative work.
从事大量创意工作的平台
And now you can automate the everyday stuff
现在 你可以将日常工作自动化
to achieve peak productivity.
令生产力达到巅峰
You get access to a rich gallery of pre-built shortcuts
你可以访问一个丰富的快捷指令中心 其中预建的
designed just for Mac.
快捷指令专为 Mac 设计
You can set up a shortcut to instantly share selected files
你可以创建一个快捷指令 即刻与朋友
with your friends so they never miss a moment.
共享选定的文件 以免错过关键时刻
And with the Shortcuts Editor,
使用快捷指令编辑器
you can easily link together a series of actions
你可以将一系列操作轻松衔接起来
to design shortcuts for your specific workflows.
为特定工作流程设计快捷指令
For instance, if you're a designer,
比如 如果你是设计师
get right to work with a shortcut
可以使用快捷指令完成工作
that opens Pinterest in one window,
一个窗口打开 Pinterest
Affinity Photo in another,
另一个窗口打开 Affinity Photo
and starts your favorite playlist in Apple Music.
同时 Apple Music 开始播放心仪歌单
All in one click.
点击一下 全部完成
We've weaved Shortcuts throughout macOS,
快捷指令贯穿整个 macOS
so you can run them no matter what app is open.
无论打开哪个 app 均可运行
They're in Finder, the Menu Bar,
快捷指令集成于访达 菜单栏
Spotlight, and of course,
聚焦搜索 当然你也可以
you can ask Siri to run them hands-free.
向 Siri 发号施令 完全摆脱双手
Shortcuts is the future of automation on Mac,
快捷指令是 Mac 自动化的发展方向
and this is just the start of a multi-year transition.
这只不过是多年过渡进程的开端
Automator will continue to be supported,
自动操作将继续获得支持
and you can import Automator workflows into Shortcuts
从第一天起 你就可以将自动操作工作流程
beginning day one.
导入快捷指令
With Shortcuts, there are more ways than ever
有了快捷指令
to create, express yourself,
创意 表达自己
and get stuff done.
完成任务的方式比以往更多
Finally, we have some really big news
最后 我们有一些重大宣布
about an app that's central to the Mac experience--
关于和 Mac 核心体验有关的一个 app
Safari.
Safari 浏览器
We built Safari from the very beginning
我们最初就开始打造 Safari 浏览器
to provide the best browsing experience on Mac,
呈现 Mac 上的最佳浏览体验
and it continues to blow the competition out of the water.
它将继续在竞争中脱颖而出
Safari is the world's fastest browser.
Safari 是世界上速度最快的浏览器
It makes navigating even the most complex websites
哪怕是浏览最复杂的网站
lightning fast.
也快如闪电
And Safari is known for its legendary power efficiency.
Safari 浏览器以突出省电性能闻名
On an M1 MacBook Pro,
在搭载 M1 芯片的 MacBook pro 上
Safari users can get up to 17 hours of browsing
Safari 浏览器可使用长达 17 个小时
And of course, Safari sets the bar
当然 Safari 浏览器
for user privacy on the web
为保护用户在网络中隐私的树立了标杆
with features like Privacy Report
凭借隐私报告
and Intelligent Tracking Prevention.
和智能防跟踪等功能
Our users are doing more in the browser than ever before--
用户能在浏览器中完成多于以往的
work, school, shopping, and entertainment.
工作、学习、购物、娱乐
And that often leaves them with a lot of tabs, windows,
这样通常会打开许多标签页 窗口
and other distractions.
以及其他令人分心的内容
We think using the browser should feel natural
我们认为 浏览器使用应给人以
and uncluttered,
自然有序之感
so we've reimagined the browsing experience.
因此 我们重塑了浏览体验
We distilled the toolbar to is essential elements.
我们提炼工具栏上的基本元素
Tabs are more compact, modern, and lightweight.
标签页更紧凑 更现代 更轻巧
And there's a completely new way to use tabs
标签页组带来标签页
with Tab Groups.
全新使用方式
They allow you to easily save and manage your tabs
便于你轻松共享和管理标签页
without cluttering up your tab bar.
避免标签页栏杂乱无章
I'll hand it over to Beth to show it in action.
下面有请 Beth 为你演示
[Beth] Thanks, Craig.
谢谢 Craig
Let's start with Safari's
我们先介绍 Safari 浏览器
gorgeous new tab design.
绚丽的全新标签页设计
All of my tabs are right here in the new streamlined tab bar.
所有标签页都在 全新的精简标签页栏中
One of the really cool things we did this year
今年的一项卓越创新是
is we built the search field right into the active tab.
搜索栏集成入活动标签页
Safari is more space efficient than ever,
Safari 浏览器空间利用比以往更高效
and I can see more of the page.
我可以看到页面上的更多内容
I can click on the active tab to see the page's full address,
我可以点击活动标签页 查看页面的完整地址
and then I can search right from here.
然后直接在这里搜索
Reader is in the tab bar whenever I need it,
随时可以调取标签页栏中的阅读器
and everything else is right here in the More menu.
其他所有选项都在“更多”菜单中
Check this out. As I switch tabs,
请看 切换标签页时
the tab bar takes on the color of the site that I'm viewing,
标签页栏显示当前站点的色彩
so it feels like a part of the page.
感觉像是融入页面之中
It looks beautiful.
视觉效果优美
Next, I'm so excited to tell you about Tab Groups.
很高兴为你介绍标签页组
Tab Groups are an easy and lightweight way
标签页组以便捷轻巧的方式
to save your tabs and pick them back up later.
保存标签页 以便稍后浏览
I'll open the new redesigned side bar,
我打开重新设计的边栏
and I have a few Tab Groups here already.
这里已经有几个标签页组
Each of these groups is a whole set of tabs.
每组里面全都是标签页
I use them for meal planning,
我用它们计划膳食
for news,
阅读新闻
and gift shopping.
购买礼物
Here in my open tabs,
在打开的标签页中
I'm planning a road trip to Los Angeles,
我在策划洛杉矶公路之旅
and I'm not done with my research yet.
但还没研究好
I can save these into a Tab Group
我可以把这些保存到标签页组中
and come back to it later.
稍后再看
I'll click the new Tab Group button
我点击新建标签页组按钮
and call this Trip to L.A.
命名为“洛杉矶之行”
What's so powerful about Tab Groups
标签页组优秀之处在于
is that they're on all of my devices.
适用于所有设备
I've got my MacBook here, and look.
我拿来了自己的 MacBook 请看
My new Tab Group is here already.
我新建的标签页组已经在这里了
As I make changes to my Tab Groups,
修改标签页组时
they update everywhere.
改动会更新到各处
I'm gonna open a bunch of tabs,
我要打开许多个标签页
and my iMac just keeps up.
iMac 上也立马打开
And if I change my current tab,
如果我修改了当前标签页
my Tab Group is always up to date,
标签页组则始终保持最新
and I never miss a thing.
绝不会错过任何内容
I can't wait to share these trip ideas with my family,
我迫不及待想与家人分享这些旅行想法
and I can just drag this Tab Group into an email
我只需把这个标签页组拖入电子邮件
and send it off.
然后发送出去
Once you start using Tab Groups,
一旦你开始使用标签页组
we know you're going to wanna get to them all the time.
我们相信 你会一直用下去
So we made it super easy to switch from right here
从标签页栏切换
in the tab bar.
十分方便
That's the new Safari on Mac.
这就是 Mac 上全新的 Safari 浏览器
We didn't stop there, though.
但精彩远没有结束
Back to Craig to tell you more.
下面有请 Craig 为你详细介绍
[Craig] Thanks, Beth.
谢谢 Beth
When we were designing the new tab experience,
设计全新标签页体验时
we wanted to build something that worked consistently
我们希望建立一种一致的使用体验 从 Mac 切换到
when you switch from your Mac to your iPhone or iPad.
iPhone 或 iPad 时 能继续手头的工作
On iPad, the new tabs and tab bar
在 iPad 上使用全新标签页和
work just like they do on Mac.
标签页栏 就像在 Mac 上一样
Tab Groups are especially helpful on iPad,
标签页组在 iPad 上特别实用
and the instant syncing
而即时同步功能
means that you can continue a project from anywhere.
便于你在任何设备上继续推进项目
On iPhone, we've done something really special.
我们在 iPhone 上做了特别设计
We took all the thinking that went into Mac and iPad
我们综合了 Mac 和 iPad 的设计理念
and pushed the envelope even further.
达到极致之余 朝前更进一步
For this smaller screen size,
针对小屏
we're introducing something that's easier to reach
我们采用更易接触的设计
and maximizes the page onscreen.
并将屏幕上的页面最大化
The new tab bar appears with just a tap
只需轻点一下 新的标签页栏
and fits directly under your thumb.
就会出现在大拇指之下
And when you scroll, the bar moves seamlessly out of the way.
滚动时 标签页栏会无缝移出页面
It's now easier and more natural to access your other tabs too.
访问其他标签页也更方便 更自然
You can just swipe over on the tab bar
只需轻扫标签页栏
to quickly move between them.
即可在标签页之间快速切换
Or swipe up on the tab bar
或向上轻扫标签页栏
to reveal a brand-new grid view of all your tabs
显示全新网格视图 包含所有标签页
plus your Tab Groups.
和标签页组
When you get to the end of your tabs,
到达标签页末尾时
you can swipe again to open a new one,
再轻扫一下 即可打开新页面
and the new customizable start page syncs with Mac
全新开始页面可自定义内容 且与 Mac 同步
so you have the same Safari experience everywhere.
因此 无论在哪里 都有相同的 Safari 浏览器体验
There's one last feature
我们今天要介绍的
that we're really excited to share--
最后一项功能是
Extensions.
扩展
Mac users love to deeply customize Safari
Mac 用户喜爱深度自定义 Safari 浏览器
with extensions like Grammarly,
使用 Grammarly
Honey, and Momentum.
Honey、Momentum 等扩展程序
And now, we're bringing web extensions to iPhone and iPad.
现在 我们为 iPhone 和 iPad 带来网页扩展程序
Just like on Mac, you choose what websites
就像使用 Mac 你可以选择哪些网站
you want extensions to be active on,
要开启扩展程序
and developers can easily tap into
而开发者可轻松开拓
and entirely new audience
全新受众
because these extensions can share code
因为这些扩展程序能与 Safari 浏览器
with existing Safari web extensions.
现有网页拓展程序共享代码
This is a huge year for Safari.
今年是 Safari 浏览器的重要年份
A totally new tab design and Tab Groups
全新设计的标签页和标签页组
simplify your browsing.
简化了浏览步骤
And Safari is more customizable than ever
凭借 iOS 和 iPadOS 上的全新开始页面
with the new start page
和扩展程序
and extensions on iOS and iPadOS.
Safari 浏览器比以往更可自定义
And with that,
接下来
we have macOS Monterey.
这就是 macOS Monterey
It's a fantastic release with great new features
完善的版本和优秀的全新功能
that help Mac users do more than ever.
帮助 Mac 用户更胜一筹
You can work across Mac and your other devices
在 Mac 与其他设备之间顺畅工作
using Universal Control and AirPlay to Mac.
使用 Universal Control 和 隔空播放到 Mac
It's easy to get productive and creative using Shortcuts
轻松获得生产力和创造力
and a totally new design for Safari,
全凭快捷指令和全新设计的 Safari 浏览器
along with incredible features like SharePlay,
以及优秀功能 比如 SharePlay
Shared with You, Focus, and Quick Note.
与你共享 专注模式和快速备忘录
We do have more to share with you,
我们的确还有许多内容要与你分享
but first, let's get outta here.
但我们先离开这里
Probably should've just taken the car.
也许得开车
As I mentioned a moment ago,
如我之前所述
we've made incredible advances in macOS
今年 我们在 macOS 和
and across all of our platforms this year.
所有平台上 都取得了傲人进步
These are going to be amazing for users,
用户感到惊喜之余
but they also create new opportunities
还为开发者创造了
for our developers,
全新机会
the heart and soul of WWDC.
这是举办 WWDC 的初衷
And to tell you about the new developer features,
为了向你介绍全新开发者功能
and technologies we've been building
以及帮助你把 app
to help you take your apps to the next level,
提升到全新水平的技术
here's our VP of WWDR,
下面有请 VP of WWDR
Susan Prescott.
Susan Prescott
[Susan] It's such a privilege to come together
很高兴能和
with our developer community
全球开发者社区相聚
and to connect with your creative energy.
让大家的创意能力交流融会
Over the course of the week, Apple engineers
这一周 Apple 工程师
are gonna share all kinds of exciting new technologies
将介绍各种令人雀跃的
and features that we think you're gonna love.
全新技术和功能 希望大家喜欢
And there are a few announcements
但我迫不及待想分享
that we just couldn't wait to share--
几条好消息
APIs that'll help you create even more incredible apps,
包括各类有助于打造更出色 app 的 API
Swift features that make the language
令编程语言更便捷
both easier and more powerful,
更强大的各类 Swift 功能
and App Store features
帮助你更贴近用户的
that'll help you better connect with users.
各类 App Store 功能
Let's start with APIs,
我们先来看 API
and there are a lot of new APIs this year.
今年将推出许多全新 API
Like the ones for SharePlay
例如 SharePlay 的各种 API
that make it possible to build new shared experiences
打造全新共享体验
for iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple TV.
惠及 iPhone、iPad、Mac、Apple TV
And system-level enhancements like Voice Isolation,
系统级的功能优化
Wide Spectrum audio, and Portrait Mode
例如语音突显 宽频谱音频和人像模式
that can work in any videoconferencing app.
任何视频会议 app 均可使用
New APIs for Focus and Notifications.
专注模式和各类通知的全新 API
A new extra-large widget size for iPad.
全新超大且专为 iPad 设计的小组件尺寸
The Screen Time API,
屏幕使用时间 API
Always-On apps for watchOS.
watchOS 上的各类全天候 app
New advanced rendering APIs in RealityKit.
RealityKit 中各类全新先进的渲染 API
And we've gone even further in this release
此外在这一版本中 我们更进一步
to make it easy for all developers
便于所有开发者
to create realistic 3D objects with Object Capture.
使用 Object Capture 创建逼真的 3D 对象
Object Capture is a revolutionary new API
Object Capture 是 macOS 上的
on macOS.
一个突破性的全新 API
Rather than manually creating 3D models which can take weeks,
相比于花数周时间手动创建 3D 模型
Object Capture uses photogrammetry
Object Capture 运用摄影制图法
to turn a series of 2D images
将一系列 2D 图像
into photorealistic 3D objects in just minutes.
变成逼真的 3D 物体 只需几分钟时间
Leading developers like Maxon and Unity
Maxon 和 Unity 等领先开发商
are already using Object Capture
已经在使用 Object Capture
to unlock entirely new ways of creating 3D content.
解锁创建 3D 内容的全新方式
It's as simple as taking photos of an object
只需拿起 iPhone 或 iPad
on your iPhone or iPad,
拍摄物体的照片
an AR preview of the model
确保在现场
while on location.
Wayfair 在使用
This will allow Wayfair users
就可以通过 AR 技术
are built using Swift.
均使用 Swift 编译
To tell you about the improvements
下面有请 Ted 为你介绍今年的改进
[Ted] Thanks, Susan.
谢谢 Susan
We designed Swift to make it easy to create great apps.
我们设计 Swift 旨在轻松创建出色 app
It has an approachable modern syntax,
其具有简单易懂的现代语法
incredible runtime performance,
出众的运行时性能
and safety features that eliminate
及杜绝各种编程错误的
whole categories of programming errors.
安全功能
In recent years, we've worked
近年来 我们携手
with the Swift open-source community
Swift 开源社区
to build tons of new features
构建许多全新功能
that make Swift easier and more powerful.
令 Swift 更便捷 更完善
And this year, one of the biggest features
今年 我们在 Swift 中构建的
we're building into Swift is Concurrency.
其中一项最大功能是并发
Concurrency is one of the most requested features for Swift,
并发是呼声最高希望加入 Swift 的功能
and it's key to building apps
这一关键功能可以用来打造
that are responsive to user input
能及时响应用户输入的 app
while doing work in the background.
同时在后台完成工作
Concurrency also makes it dramatically easier
有了并发功能
to write code that does work in parallel,
编写可并行工作的代码十分方便
so your app can take full advantage
你编译的 app 可充分利用
of multi-core processors.
多核处理器
Without language features that simplify concurrency,
如果没有简化并发的语言功能
you need to write "asynchronous" code
你需要编写异步代码
that's hard to write, hard to understand,
这种代码难写 难理解
and hard to debug.
又难调试
Our approach to concurrency in Swift
我们使用 Swift 构建并发的方法
builds on the same core principles of Swift itself,
与 Swift 本身的核心原则相同
making it easier to write fast, modern,
更易编写快速、现代、安全的代码
safe code with fewer mistakes.
同时减少错误
We built structured concurrency deep into the Swift language
我们深入运用 Swift 语言 构建结构化并发
and use the common async/await pattern
采用常见的 async/await 模式
combined with a technology called actors.
与 actors 技术相结合
This means you can write code as a simple sequence of steps
你可以按简单的步骤顺序编写代码
with actors safely isolating parallel tasks from one another.
actors 可将并行任务相互安全隔离
So building code for concurrency
编译并发代码
goes from something complicated like this
化繁
to something simple like this.
为简
That kind of power and simplicity
这种高效简单
is what Swift is all about,
是 Swift 的优点
and we're excited to share more with you this week.
在这个星期里 我们将为你深入介绍
Now, back to Susan.
现在 把镜头交还给 Susan
[Susan] We created Swift and all these other
我们创造 Swift 及其他所有
technologies and frameworks for one reason:
技术和框架只有一个原因
to help you build the best possible apps.
帮助你打造出更好的 app
And the best place to discover those apps
探索这些 app 最合适的地方
is on the App Store.
自然是 App Store
To tell you about some of the exciting features
下面有请 Ann 为你介绍一些
we've been working on, here's Ann.
我们一直在努力的精彩功能
[Ann] Since the beginning, we designed the App Store
从一开始 我们就把 App Store
to be a safe and trusted place.
设计成安全且值得信赖的平台
Users can just focus on finding the right app,
用户只需一心寻找合适的 app
knowing Apple has reviewed every app
因为 Apple 审查了每款 app
to make sure it meets our high standards
确保其符合在保障
for security, privacy, and safety.
隐私和安全方面的高标准
And that's why the App Store now serves
因此 App Store 每周迎来
nearly 600 million weekly visitors
近 6 亿访客
in 175 countries and regions,
来自 175 个国家或地区
making it a great business opportunity
给所有开发者带来
for all developers,
巨大商机
and an engine for innovation and growth.
亦成为创新和增长的引擎
And Apple has now paid over $230 billion to developers
2300 多亿美元 这是自 App Store 问世以来
since the App Store launched.
Apple 向开发者支付的数额
Today, we're introducing some incredible new ways
今天 我们将介绍一些
to help developers like you reach even more users,
帮助开发者惠及更多用户的全新方式
starting with the App Product Page.
首先是 App 产品页面
This year, you'll be able to create
今年 你将能创建
multiple custom product pages
多个自定义产品页面
to showcase different features of your app for different users.
为不同用户展示 app 的不同功能
You can also try out different screenshots,
你还可以尝试不同截图
videos, and even app icons
视频 甚至 app 图标
to understand what users like most.
了解用户最喜欢哪样的
These improvements will give you even more ways
这些改进将给予你
to tell the world about your app.
更多推广 app 的方式
It's also important to showcase the dynamic things happening
另外展示 app 内开展的动态活动
inside your apps.
也是很重要的一件事
The most popular apps and games
各类受欢迎的 app 和游戏
are constantly introducing new content
都会经常推出新内容
and limited-time events
和限时活动
like Pokémon Go Fest,
比如 Pokémon Go Fest
film premieres like In the Heights
In the Heights 等电影首映礼
and Nike fitness challenges.
和 Nike 健身挑战
Events across the entire app ecosystem
整个 app 生态系统活动不断
help users find the next big thing.
帮助用户找到下一大事件
This year, we're introducing new ways
我们将在 iOS 15 中推出探索 此类精彩活动的全新方式
We call them In-App Events.
这就是 APP 内精彩活动
With In-App Events, the dynamic content
有了 APP 内精彩活动
and experiences within apps
app 内的动态内容和体验
will be front and center on the App Store
将会在 App Store 中重点展示
so users never miss a big moment.
让用户们不错过精彩时刻
And this is huge for developers.
这对开发者们来说也意味深远
In-App Events can be surfaced throughout the store
APP 内精彩活动 可面向整个 Store 内
to millions of users, whether they're brand-new to the app
数百万用户宣传
or they use it every day.
无论是 app 新用户 还是日常用户
You can showcase them on your app's product page.
你可在 app 产品页面展示
Users can learn more, sign up to be notified,
用户可详细了解 注册开启通知
or quickly join the action if it's happening now.
如果活动正在进行也可以直接加入
They can discover events
用户会收到基于个性化的推荐
with personalized recommendations.
来探索活动
And in Search.
也可以在搜索中发现
Our expert editors will curate the best and biggest events.
我们的专业编辑将精选推荐各类精彩的大规模活动
And the new App Store widget
全新 App Store 小组件
will feature upcoming events right on the home screen.
将在主屏幕上特别展示即将举办的活动
With In-App Events, the App Store continues to be
凭借 APP 内精彩活动 App Store 持续不断的成为
the best place to discover what's happening
探索 app 和游戏内当前活动的
in apps and games.
最佳平台
And this will be open to all developers,
APP 内精彩活动 对所有开发者开放
whether they already have events,
无论是已举办活动
or they're just getting started.
还是刚开始活动
And now I'll hand it back to Susan.
把镜头交还给 Susan
[Susan] There's something else we're doing this year,
今年 我们还在做另一件事
and it's going to take app development
其会将 app 开发
to the next level.
提升到更高水准
It integrates the Cloud with our developer tools
以强大的新方式将各类开发者工具
in a powerful new way, and it's called...
整合到云端
Xcode Cloud.
这就是 Xcode Cloud
Today, creating an app requires multiple steps--
今天 创建一款 app 需要多个步骤
building, testing, and delivery--
编译、测试和交付
and a number of different tools.
以及许多不同工具
Xcode Cloud simplifies the workflow
Xcode Cloud 融合所有功能
by bringing everything together,
简化工作流程
so as an individual developer,
所以 身为个人开发者
you can focus your energy on being creative
你可以集中精力去创新
and development teams can collaborate more effectively.
而开发团队可以更有效协作
Here's how it works.
来看看它是这么工作的
When you commit a change to your code,
提交代码修改时
Xcode Cloud can automatically build the app.
Xcode Cloud 可以自动编译 app
Because it's built in the Cloud,
因为在云端编译
your Mac is free for other tasks.
Mac 可以处理其他任务
And for teams, everyone can see
每位团队成员都能看到
if the change introduces errors,
修改是否引发错误
so everyone can find and fix issues faster.
所以大家都能更快发现和修复问题
Then Xcode Cloud runs your automated tests in parallel
然后 Xcode Cloud 并行运行自动测试
so they complete in a fraction of the time
即便模拟在各大 Apple
even as they simulate running
设备和平台上运行
on every kind of Apple device and platform.
只需一小会儿就能完成
And the test results are displayed in Xcode,
测试结果显示于 Xcode
so you can easily see what worked
便于你了解哪些代码有效
and fix what didn't.
和修复有问题的代码
Finally, once the app passes all its tests,
最后 app 通过所有测试之后
Xcode Cloud can automatically distribute it
Xcode Cloud 可通过 TestFlight 将 app 自动分发给
to the testers on your team,
团队中的测试人员
and even external beta testers, with TestFlight.
甚至外部测试人员
And all of these essential continuous integration
Xcode 自带所有这些基本的
and delivery features are right there in Xcode.
持续集成和交付功能
So you can work without switching tools
这样你在工作时就不需要在各种工具切换
and you can stay focused on your code.
只需集中精力用来编程
Xcode Cloud is the quickest, easiest way
Xcode Cloud 是编译、测试和交付 app
to build, test, and deliver your apps.
最快速 最简单的途径
And it's built with advanced security
并采用先进的安全功能
to protect you and your projects.
保护你和项目的安全
Your source code is only used in a temporary build environment,
源代码仅用于临时编译环境
and the only things Xcode Cloud stores
Xcode Cloud 仅保留
are the products of the build.
编译好的产品
Xcode Cloud and TestFlight
Xcode Cloud 结合 TestFlight
make it easy to distribute betas to users
将测试版轻松分发给使用
on iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, and Apple TV,
iPhone、iPad、Apple Watch 和 Apple TV 的用户
and we want Xcode Cloud to be able
我们还希望 Xcode Cloud
to automatically distribute beta apps
能跨所有 Apple 平台
across all Apple platforms.
自动分发测试版 app
To make that happen,
为了实现这点
we're bringing TestFlight to the Mac.
我们为 Mac 带来 TestFlight
So you can use TestFlight to easily test your Mac apps,
你可以使用 TestFlight 轻松测试 Mac app
including features like In-app purchases.
包括 APP 内购买等功能
Xcode Cloud is incredibly powerful,
Xcode Cloud 功能十分强大
and we can't wait for you to use it
我们迫不及待地能看到你
and see how it'll help you build better apps faster.
用它来更快捷地打造出更出色的各类 app
We'll be providing access to a limited beta starting today
今天起 我们将提供访问有限测试版的机会
and expanding access to this free beta
今年夏秋将扩大这一免费测试版的
throughout the summer and fall.
访问人数
And Xcode Cloud will be available
Xcode Cloud 将于明年
to all developers next year.
提供给所有开发者
We'll provide more details on pricing and availability
今年秋天 我们将提供更多定价
this fall.
以及正式推出时间的细节
We're really excited about these announcements,
我们十分高兴介绍上述全新功能
and these are just some of the highlights.
而这些功能只是其中一些亮点
We continue to innovate with the App Store
我们在 App Store 以及
and tools and technologies to help you
工具和技术方面不断创新
do extraordinary things.
帮助你取得非凡成就
And we're gonna be telling you even more
我们将在本周的
in sessions throughout the week.
各类 session 进行更详细的介绍
Now, back to Tim.
把镜头交还给 Tim
But first... [snaps]
稍等
Much better.
好多了
Take it home, Tim.
有请在主会场的 Tim
[Tim] Thank you, Susan. And thank you, Craig.
谢谢 Susan 谢谢 Craig
And thanks to all of our presenters.
感谢所有演讲者
for our users and our developers.
这是用户和开发者的重要日子
We took giant steps forward
我们的各类软件平台
with all of our software platforms,
翻开了新的一页
and they will enable our users and developers
进一步帮助用户和开发者
to do remarkable things.
取得傲人成就
Our OS releases will be available
各大 OS 的开发者测试版
as developer betas today.
将于今天推出
And each of them will have a public beta next month.
各大 OS 公开测试版将于下月推出
And all of this incredible software
所有这些优秀软件
will be available to all of our users this fall.
将于今秋提供给所有用户
I'm so excited for these new releases
我非常期待这些新版本的推出
and how they will make our products even more powerful
并将我们的产品变得更强大
and more capable.
更多用
They will provide users new ways to enrich their lives
它们将以全新方式丰富用户生活
and developers new tools to change the world.
为开发者提供改变世界的新工具
We hope you've enjoyed today's event
希望你喜爱今天的活动
and that you're excited for the week ahead.
尽享令人雀跃的一周盛会
For those developers who want to take a deeper dive
开发者若想深入了解
into our announcements,
全新功能
we have the Platforms State of the Union
敬请期待今天稍晚召开的
coming up later today.
Platforms State of the Union
And we have a week full of in-depth sessions
这一周里 我们将举办各种 session
and one-to-one labs with Apple engineers.
各类与 Apple 工程师的 1:1 lab
We will also provide Pavilions, Daily Recaps,
还有各种 Pavilions、Daily Recaps
and other experiences
和其他体验活动
to help you get the most out of the conference.
帮助你在整个 WWDC 中收获更多
Thank you for joining us. Let's have a great week!
感谢加入我们 祝你拥有美好的一周